<institutions xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
 xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="authority_schema.xsd">
	<institution>
		<id>540</id>
		<name>The Cato Institute</name>
		<blurb>Founded in 1977, the Cato Institute is a nonpartisan public policy research foundation headquartered in Washington, D.C. The Institute is named for Cato&#039;s Letters, libertarian pamphlets that helped lay the philosophical foundation for the American Revolution. The Cato Institute seeks to broaden the parameters of public policy debate to allow consideration of more options that are consistent with the traditional American principles of limited government, individual liberty, and peace. Toward that goal, the Institute strives to involve the intelligent, concerned lay public in questions of policy and the proper role of government. The Cato Institute undertakes an extensive publications program dealing with the complete spectrum of policy issues. Books, monographs, and shorter studies are commissioned to examine the federal budget, Social Security, monetary policy, natural resource policy, military spending, regulation, NATO, international trade, and myriad other issues. Major policy conferences are held throughout the year, from which papers are published thrice yearly in the Cato Journal. The Institute also publishes the quarterly magazine Regulation.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cato.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>541</id>
		<name>Carnegie Endowment for International Peace</name>
		<blurb>The Carnegie Endowment for International Peace was established in 1910 in Washington, D.C., with a gift from Andrew Carnegie. As a tax-exempt operating (not grant-making) foundation, the Endowment conducts programs of research, discussion, publication, and education in international affairs and U.S. foreign policy. Carnegie&#039;s senior associates whose backgrounds include government, journalism, law, academia, and public affairs bring to their work substantial first-hand experience in foreign policy. Through writing, public and media appearances, study groups, and conferences, Carnegie associates seek to invigorate and extend both expert and public discussion on a wide range of international issues. These include worldwide migration, nuclear nonproliferation, regional conflicts, multilateralism, democracy building, and the use of force. The Endowment also engages in and encourages projects designed to foster innovative contributions in international affairs.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.carnegieendowment.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>544</id>
		<name>University of British Columbia</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url></url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>545</id>
		<name>Academy of Political Science</name>
		<blurb>The Academy of Political Science (APS), founded in 1880, promotes objective, scholarly analyses of political, social, and economic issues. Through its conferences and publications APS provides analysis and insight into both domestic and foreign policy issues. Due to its well established effort to provide analysis on domestic and foreign affairs, the Academy enjoys a special prestige among the many institutions, committees and think tanks devoted to the exploration and exposition of public policy. More important than mere longevity are the depth and breadth of intellectual competence that the Academy&#039;s members bring to their chosen fields. Furthermore, there is the assurance that all publications of the Academy are not shaped by ideological or partisan considerations.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.psqonline.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>547</id>
		<name>Carnegie Council</name>
		<blurb>The Carnegie Council is the leading voice promoting ethical leadership on issues of war, peace, religion in politics, and global social justice. MISSION. The Carnegie Council&#039;s mission is to be the voice for ethics in international policy. It convenes agenda-setting forums and creates educational opportunities and information resources for a worldwide audience of teachers and students, journalists, international affairs professionals, and concerned citizens.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cceia.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>548</id>
		<name>The International Institute for Strategic Studies</name>
		<blurb>The International Institute for Strategic Studies (IISS) is the world&#039;s leading authority on political-military conflict.The IISS, based in London, is both a limited company in UK law and a registered charity. It has offices in the US and in Singapore with charitable status in each jurisdiction.The IISS was founded in 1958 in the UK by a number of individuals interested in how to maintain civilised international relations in the nuclear age. Much of the Institute&#039;s early work focused on nuclear deterrence and arms control and was hugely influential in setting the intellectual structures for managing the Cold War.The Institute grew dramatically during the 1980s and 1990s, expanding both because of the nature of its work and its geographical scope. Its mandate became to look at the problems of conflict, however caused, that might have an important military content. This gave fresh impetus to the Institute as it began to cover more comprehensively political and military issues in all continents. As this mandate developed, the Institute worked hard both to provide the best information and analysis on strategic trends, and to facilitate contacts between government leaders, business people and analysts that would lead to the development of better public policy in the fields of international relations and international security.The IISS is the primary source of accurate, objective information on international strategic issues for politicians and diplomats, foreign affairs analysts, international business, economists, the military, defence commentators, journalists, academics and the informed public. The Institute owes no allegiance to any government, or to any political or other organisation.The Institute&#039;s high-profile publications are both timely and authoritative. They are universally regarded as providing the best independent, internationally sourced information and commentary on the main strategic events touching on national, regional and global security.The Institute&#039;s conference activities are considered to be at the forefront of public policy development, especially given that its convening power is such that it can often bring government officials and others together in formats and circumstances that they could not easily manage for themselves.The Institute&#039;s staff and governing boards are international and its network of some 2,500 Individual Members and 450 Corporate and Institutional Members is drawn from more than 100 countries. The IISS, through its various activities, seeks to provide excellent information and analysis that can improve wider public understanding of international security problems and through its network, influence the development of sounder public policy.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.iiss.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>549</id>
		<name>Chatham House</name>
		<blurb>Chatham House has been the home of the Royal Institute of Institute of International Affairs for over eight decades. Our mission is to be world-leading source of independent analysis, informed debate and influential ideas on how to build a prosperous and secure world for all. Chatham House pursues its mission: by drawing on its membership to promote open as well as confidential debates about significant developments in international affairs and about the context and content of policy responses; by producing independent and rigorous analysis of critical global, regional and country-specific challenges; by offering new ideas to decision-makers and-shapers on how these could best be tackled from the near to long term. Founded in 1920 and based in St James&#039;s Square in London, Chatham House celebrated the 80th anniversary of the granting of its Royal Charter in 2006. The Chatham House Rule, famous worldwide for facilitating free speech and confidentiality at meetings, originated here.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.chathamhouse.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>550</id>
		<name>The Institute for Defence Studies and Analyses</name>
		<blurb>The Institute for Defence Studies and Analyses (IDSA) was established as a registered society in New Delhi on November 11 1965. It is considered to be the premier strategic and security studies Think Tank in India. Over the years the Institute has enlarged its focus of research from Defence Studies to cover issues of National and International Security. The Institute is funded by the Indian Ministry of Defence, but functions autonomously. Apart from research, the Institute also provides training programmes to civilian and military officers of the Government of India. The Indian Parliament&#039;s Standing Committee on Defence frequently utilises the expertise of the Institute.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.idsa.in</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>551</id>
		<name>Faculty of Humanities, Development and Social Sciences, University of KwaZulu-Natal, South Africa</name>
		<blurb>The new University of KwaZulu-Natal unites two major educational institutions in KwaZulu-Natal â the University of Natal and the University of Durban-Westville.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ukzn.ac.za/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>552</id>
		<name>ARI Movement  [archived]</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.ari.org.tr/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>553</id>
		<name>U.S. Department of State, Bureau of International Information Programs</name>
		<blurb>State Department&#039;s Bureau of International Information Programs (IIP) engages international audiences on issues of foreign policy, society and values to help create an environment receptive to U.S. national interests.
IIP communicates with foreign opinion makers and other publics through a wide range of print and electronic outreach materials published in English, Arabic, Chinese, French, Persian, Russian, and Spanish. IIP also provides information outreach support to U.S. embassies and consulates in more than 140 countries worldwide.</blurb>
		<url>http://usinfo.state.gov</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>556</id>
		<name>World Policy Institute</name>
		<blurb>Since joining the New School for Social Research in 1991, the World Policy Institute has adapted its traditional mission of policy research and advocacy on critical world problems to the New School&#039;s tradition of creative adult education. It has done so at a time when the traditional subject of international diplomacy and world politics itself is being transformed by dramatic world changes from the end of the Cold War to the increasing blurring of the line between domestic and international concerns. Accordingly, the Institute has both redefined its agenda and broadened its mission.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.worldpolicy.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>557</id>
		<name>United Nations University</name>
		<blurb>UNU is dedicated to the generation and transfer of knowledge, and the strengthening of individual and institutional capacities in furtherance of the purposes and principles of the Charter of the United Nations. The mission of UNU is to contribute, through research and capacity building, to efforts to resolve the pressing global problems that are a concern of the United Nations, its Peoples and Member States.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.unu.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>558</id>
		<name>Center for Strategic and International Studies</name>
		<blurb>For four decades, the Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) has been dedicated to providing world leaders with strategic insights on-and policy solutions to-current and emerging global issues. CSIS is led by John J. Hamre, former U.S. deputy secretary of defense. It is guided by a board of trustees chaired by former U.S. senator Sam Nunn and consisting of prominent individuals from both the public and private sectors. The CSIS staff of 190 researchers and support staff focus primarily on three subject areas. First, CSIS addresses the full spectrum of new challenges to national and international security. Second, it maintains resident experts on all of the world&#039;s major geographical regions. Third, it is committed to helping to develop new methods of governance for the global age; to this end, CSIS has programs on technology and public policy, international trade and finance, and energy. Headquartered in Washington, D.C., CSIS is private, bipartisan, and tax-exempt.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.csis.org</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>559</id>
		<name>Center for Contemporary Conflict</name>
		<blurb>The Center for Contemporary Conflict (CCC) conducts research on current and emerging security issues and conveys its findings to U.S. and Allied policy-makers and military forces. Launched by the Naval Postgraduate School&#039;s Department of National Security Affairs in 2001 and propelled by a seasoned staff with ready access to military and academic circles, the CCC is uniquely positioned to develop security research of high quality and relevance. Through aggressive outreach highlighted by our Regional Security Education Program (RSEP), the CCC ensures that its analyses benefit the makers and executers of U.S. defense policy. Active in the academy and in the field, the CCC bridges the gap between the security researcher and the warfighter to the benefit of both.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ccc.nps.navy.mil</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>560</id>
		<name>Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs, Princeton University</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://wws.princeton.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>561</id>
		<name>Institute for Palestine Studies</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.palestine-studies.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>562</id>
		<name>Cultures  Conflits</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.conflits.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>563</id>
		<name>Belfer Center for Science and International Affairs, Harvard University</name>
		<blurb>The Belfer Center for Science and International Affairs (BCSIA) is the hub of research, teaching, and training in international security affairs, environmental and resource issues, science and technology policy, and conflict studies at Harvard&#039;s John F. Kennedy School of Government. The Center&#039;s mission is to provide leadership in advancing policy-relevant knowledge about the most important challenges of international security and other critical issues where science, technology, and international affairs intersect. BCSIA&#039;s leadership begins with the recognition of science and technology as driving forces transforming international affairs. The Center integrates insights of social and natural scientists, technologists, and practitioners with experience in government, diplomacy, the military, and business to address these challenges.</blurb>
		<url>http://belfercenter.ksg.harvard.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>564</id>
		<name>Partnership for Peace Consortium of Defense Academies and Security Studies Institutes</name>
		<blurb>Connections: The Quarterly Journal is the flagship publication of the Partnership for Peace Consortium of Defense Academies and Security Studies Institutes. It is published on paper and online, originally in English and translated into Russian. The Journal is managed by the PfP Consortium Editorial Board and presents in-depth studies on current issues of Euroatlantic security.</blurb>
		<url>http://connections-qj.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>565</id>
		<name>Georgetown Journal of International Affairs</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url></url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>566</id>
		<name>Slovak Foreign Policy Association</name>
		<blurb>Výskumné centrum Slovenskej spoloÄnosti pre zahraniÄnú politiku, n.o. / The Research Centre of the Slovak Foreign Policy Association (RC SFPA) was founded by the Act no. 13/2002 Coll. based on the Slovak Government decision number 1113 of November 26, 2003. It was established as a non-profit organization after transformation of the Slovak MFA Institute for International Studies which was a former allowance organization. The Research Centre of the SFPA was registered in Bratislava County Council on January 30, 2004 as an organization performing publicly beneficial duties in creation, progress, protection, revitalisation and promotion of intellectual and cultural values.In accordance with the statute (Article III), the RC SFPA provides the following publicly beneficial services: 1. prepares independent expert analyses of the key questions in a field of international relations and the Slovak foreign policy; 2. publishes periodical and non-periodical publications, the role of which is to intesify knowledge in the area of international relations and the Slovak foreign policy and they are at the same time a source of credible academic information in the field of international affairs and the Slovak foreign policy suitable for specialists as well as for a lay public; 3. organises professional events and participates in the international expert debate concerning international relations and security research; 4. assists in the optimization of an academic discussion about international relations and the Slovak foreign policy; 5. provides a creative environment for the rise of a new generation of Slovak professionals in the field of international affairs; 6. encourages broader interest of Slovak citizens in global affairs and in a more profound understanding of the importance of foreign policy and its interconnection with domestic politics.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.sfpa.sk/en/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>567</id>
		<name>Council on Foreign Relations</name>
		<blurb>Mission Statement. The Council on Foreign Relations is an independent, nonpartisan membership organization, think tank, and publisher dedicated to being a resource for its members, government officials, business executives, journalists, educators and students, civic and religious leaders, and other interested citizens in order to help them better understand the world and the foreign policy choices facing the United States and other countries. Founded in 1921, the Council takes no institutional positions on matters of policy. The Council carries out its mission by: Maintaining a diverse membership, including special programs to promote interest and develop expertise in the next generation of foreign policy leaders; Convening meetings at its headquarters in New York and in Washington, DC, and other cities where senior government officials, members of Congress, global leaders, and prominent thinkers come together with Council members to discuss and debate major international issues; Supporting a Studies Program that fosters independent research, enabling Council scholars to produce articles, reports, and books and hold roundtables that analyze foreign policy issues and make concrete policy recommendations; Publishing Foreign Affairs, the preeminent journal of international affairs and U.S. foreign policy; Sponsoring Independent Task Forces that produce reports with both findings and policy prescriptions on the most important foreign policy topics; and Providing up-to-date information and analysis about world events and American foreign policy on its website, CFR.org.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cfr.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>568</id>
		<name>International Crisis Group</name>
		<blurb>The International Crisis Group (ICG) is an independent, non-profit, multinational organization, with over 90 staff members on five continents, working through field-based analysis and high-level advocacy to prevent and resolve deadly conflict.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.crisisweb.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>569</id>
		<name>Arnold A. Saltzman Institute of War and Peace Studies</name>
		<blurb>Founded in 1951 under the sponsorship of Dwight D. Eisenhower during his tenure as President of Columbia University, the Institute of War and Peace Studies (IWPS) was renamed the Arnold A. Saltzman Institute of War and Peace Studies (SIWPS) in March 2003. President Eisenhower created the Institute to promote understanding of the &quot;disastrous consequences of war upon man\&#039;s spiritual, intellectual, and material progress.&quot; The Institute has no formal teaching program; rather, its members conduct a wide variety of instructional activities through the Political Science Department and the School of International and Public Affairs (SIPA) at Columbia. Institute members offer courses on American foreign policy, national security, international politics, political economy, environmental policy, and international organization. In addition to offering courses, SIWPS Director Richard Betts coordinates the International Security Policy Concentration for SIPA, and Professor Robert Jervis serves as Deputy Chair of the Department of Political Science.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.columbia.edu/cu/siwps/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>570</id>
		<name>Jewish Institute for National Security Affairs</name>
		<blurb>The Jewish Institute for National Security Affairs (JINSA) is a non-profit, non-partisan and nonsectarian educational organization committed to explaining the need for a prudent national security policy for the United States, addressing the security requirements of both the United States and the State of Israel, and strengthening the strategic cooperation relationship between these two great democracies. Founded as a result of the lessons learned from the 1973 Yom Kippur War, JINSA communicates with the national security establishment and the general public to explain the role Israel can and does play in bolstering American interests, as well as the link between American defense policy and the security of Israel.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.jinsa.org/home/home.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>571</id>
		<name>Australian National University Department of International Relations</name>
		<blurb>The Australian National University Department of International Relations is one of the world&#039;s leading centres for research and graduate training in International Relations. ANU is also unique in combining the general theoretical and empirical study of international and global politics with a focus on political dynamics and developments in the Asia-Pacific region.</blurb>
		<url>http://ips.cap.anu.edu.au/ir/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>572</id>
		<name>Austrian National Defence Academy</name>
		<blurb>The Austrian National Defence Academy [Landesverteidigungsakademie] is the highest military training and research institution of the Austrian Armed Forces (AAF). It acts the &quot;brain trust&quot; of the AAF, and serves the forces and the MoD with: approx. 240 employees, including 35 conscripts, approx. 2,000 students, including 100 international students, 150 courses, 5-10 international events, 200 individual lectures, and more than 10,000 teaching units p. Tasks: Research and Training Basic training for higher officers is offered in: General Staff Course, Higher Quartermaster Officers&#039; Course, and the Course for Higher Military Services. Staff officers&#039; training (career and reserve) Training for leaders Teaching, research, and lectures in the fields of security, defence, and military politics Research and development in the fields of military strategy, operations, and tactics Teaching, research, and lectures in the field of security policy considering aspects of humanities and social sciences. Language training of the AAF.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.bundesheer.at/organisation/beitraege/lvak/eindex.shtml</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>573</id>
		<name>German Institute of Global and Area Studies</name>
		<blurb>The Working Paper Series serves to disseminate the research results of work in progress prior to publication to encourage the exchange of ideas and academic debate. An objective of the series is to get the findings out quickly, even if the presentations are less than fully polished. Inclusion of a paper in the Working Paper Series does not constitute publication and should not limit publication in any other venue. Copyright remains with the authors. When Working Papers are eventually accepted by or published in a journal or book, the correct citation reference and, if possible, the corresponding link will then be included in the Working Papers.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.giga-hamburg.de/workingpapers</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>574</id>
		<name>School of Oriental and African Studies - University of London</name>
		<blurb>The SOAS Department of Economics is one of the country&#039;s leading departments specialising in the economics of development and growth. Research is pursued on a variety of topics and is unique in its depth and range of regional coverage. A special feature of the Department is the orientation to Political Economy and heterodox approaches to Economics. In addition, the Department has strength in economic theory. Individual members of staff possess considerable practical expertise in econometrics, however empirical methods are not the primary focus of the Department as a whole. The Department has an active Working Paper series and a regular output of publications.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.soas.ac.uk/economics/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>575</id>
		<name>Research Center (SFB) 700</name>
		<blurb>Governance has become a central theme in social science research. Research Center SFB 700: Governance in Areas of Limited Statehood investigates governance in areas of limited statehood, i.e. developing countries, failing and failed states, as well as, in historical perspective, different types of colonies. How and under what conditions can governance deliver legitimate authority, security, and welfare, and what problems are likely to emerge? Operating since 2006 and financed by the German Research Foundation (DFG), the Research Center involves the Freie Universität Berlin, the University of Potsdam, the European University Institute, the Hertie School of Governance, the German Institute for International and Security Affairs (SWP), and the Social Science Research Center Berlin (WZB).</blurb>
		<url>http://www.sfb-governance.de/en/index.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>576</id>
		<name>SETA Foundation for Political, Economic and Social Research</name>
		<blurb>Additional Materials from SETA Foundation for Political, Economic and Social Research</blurb>
		<url>http://www.setav.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>577</id>
		<name>Athena Intelligence</name>
		<blurb>Athena Intelligence is an advanced research network on insurgency and jihadist terrorism composed of specialists coming from Universities, Spanish Armed Forces and security agencies. Athena Intelligence&#039;s aims are the following: Promoting multidisciplinary research on jihadist terrorism, Elaborating and transmitting analytical and scientific studies, Selecting and classifying information from open sources on insurgency and jhadist terrorism, Providing specialized teaching and training.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.athenaintelligence.org/spip.php?rubrique11=en</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>578</id>
		<name>NATO Defense College</name>
		<blurb>The NATO Defense College is the Alliance&#039;s flagship academic institution. It is here that senior officers and officials can prepare for NATO appointments of increasing responsibility and for the challenging multinational security environment facing NATO in the 21st century. We are keenly aware of this responsibility to the Alliance and the nations of the Partnership for Peace and Mediterranean Dialogue. We endeavour to offer an array of academic courses, research projects and Outreach programmes to meet their needs. Our core business is our Senior Course and associated shorter courses tailored to specific audiences. We concentrate on the high-level political-military issues that confront both civilian and military leadership at the Alliance and national level. We strive to promote debate, to seek consensus, and to master the skills needed to succeed in a multinational environment. It is our aspiration to be regarded as the first choice for nations in the educational development of their senior officers and officials destined for NATO and NATO-related appointments.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ndc.nato.int/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>579</id>
		<name>Lowy Institute for International Policy</name>
		<blurb>The Lowy Institute is an independent international policy think tank based in Sydney. Its objective is to generate new ideas and dialogue on international developments and Australia&#039;s role in the world. Its mandate is broad. It ranges across all the dimensions of international policy debate in Australia - economic, political and strategic - and it is not limited to a particular geographic region.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.lowyinstitute.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>580</id>
		<name>John F. Kennedy School of Government Faculty Research Working Paper Series</name>
		<blurb>The KSG Faculty Research Working Paper Series is an electronic database of working papers reflecting the broad range of research activities of Kennedy School faculty members. In addition to the Faculty Research Working Papers Series, the Kennedy School has a wide variety of working papers and other publications available through individual research centers and programs. The KSG Faculty Research Working Papers Series is intended to complement and highlight these other important research outlets.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ksg.harvard.edu/research/working_papers/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>581</id>
		<name>Istituto Affari Internazionali</name>
		<blurb>The Istituto Affari Internazionali (IAI) was founded on 11 October 1965 on the initiative of Altiero Spinelli, its first director. In 1991 the Institute moved to Palazzo Rondinini, an elegant eighteenth century Baroque building in the heart of Rome, where the main activities organized by the Institute take place. A non-profit organization, the IAI is funded by individual and corporate members, public and private organizations, major international foundations, and by a standing grant from the Italian Ministry of Foreign Affairs. The Institute&#039;s main objective is to promote an understanding of the problems of international politics through studies, research, meetings and publications, with the aim of increasing the opportunities of all countries to move in the direction of supranational organization, democratic freedom and social justice (IAI Bylaws, Article 1). The Institute offers members and non members standard and personalized services. An example of the latter is the Laboratorio di Politica Internazionale (International Affairs Laboratory).</blurb>
		<url>http://www.iai.it/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>582</id>
		<name>Center for Global Development</name>
		<blurb>CGD is an independent think tank that works to reduce global poverty and inequality by encouraging policy change in the U.S. and other rich countries through rigorous research and active engagement with the policy community.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cgdev.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>583</id>
		<name>Danish Institute for International Studies</name>
		<blurb>The Danish Institute for International Studies (DIIS) was separated from the former Danish Center for International Studies and Human Rights (DCISM) and established as an independent state research institute for international studies on January 1, 2013. DIIS carries out research and analysis on a wide range of issues within the areas of globalisation, security and development. Also, we assess Denmark&#039;s foreign and political situation and inform policymakers and the public. The management of DIIS is the responsibility of director Nanna Hvidt.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.diis.dk/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>584</id>
		<name>The Jamestown Foundation</name>
		<blurb>The Jamestown Foundation&#039;s mission is to inform and educate policy makers and the broader policy community about events and trends in those societies which are strategically or tactically important to the United States and which frequently restrict access to such information. Utilizing indigenous and primary sources, Jamestown&#039;s material is delivered without political bias, filter or agenda. It is often the only source of information which should be, but is not always, available through official or intelligence channels, especially in regard to Eurasia and terrorism.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.jamestown.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>585</id>
		<name>North Caucasus Weekly (formerly Chechnya Weekly), The Jamestown Foundation</name>
		<blurb>North Caucasus Weekly, formerly known as Chechnya Weekly, is the foundation&#039;s special coverage of the crisis in the breakaway republic. Its mission is to inform policymakers, the media, and the public of developments in Chechnya, discuss the origins of the conflict and explore the possibilities for peace. Beginning January 2003 with Volume IV, Chechnya Weekly is researched and written by Lawrence A. Uzzell, a senior Jamestown Foundation fellow who opened Jamestown&#039;s Moscow office in 1992. A specialist in the former Soviet Union since 1989, a Yale graduate and widely published in the American, British and Russian media, Uzzell is President of International Religious Freedom Watch (formerly Keston USA). Volumes I through III of Chechnya Weekly, which span 2000-2002, were researched and written by John Dunlop of the Hoover Institute at Stanford University. Dunlop has been a senior fellow at the Hoover Institution at Stanford University since 1983 and served as member of the Committee of Visitors of the Davis Center for Russian Studies at Harvard University. This publication was renamed North Caucasus Weekly in June 2008.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.jamestown.org/chechnya_weekly/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>586</id>
		<name>Columbia University Press</name>
		<blurb>Established in 1893, Columbia University Press publishes reference and scholarly books in the humanities, social sciences, and natural sciences. Since 1991 the Press has also been a leader in electronic publishing. One of the largest university presses, Columbia University Press publishes over 150 new titles per year and has a backlist of more than 3,000 books. The Press is the publisher of classic reference works including The Columbia Encyclopedia, The Columbia Granger&#039;s World of Poetry Online, and The Columbia Gazetteer of the World, as well as the works of authors such as Julia Kristeva, David Mamet, Quentin Bell, Antonio Gramsci, Theodor Adorno, Lillian Faderman, Amos Elon, Gilles Deleuze, Martin Gilbert, Andrei Sinyavsky, and John Rawls.</blurb>
		<url>http://cup.columbia.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>587</id>
		<name>Peterson Institute for International Economics</name>
		<blurb>The Peter G. Peterson Institute for International Economics is a private, nonprofit, nonpartisan research institution devoted to the study of international economic policy. Since 1981 the Institute has provided timely and objective analysis of, and concrete solutions to, a wide range of international economic problems. It is one of the very few economics think tanks that are widely regarded as &quot;nonpartisan&quot; by the press and &quot;neutral&quot; by the Congress, and it is cited by the quality media more than any other such institution.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.petersoninstitute.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>588</id>
		<name>Council of American Ambassadors</name>
		<blurb>The Ambassadors Review is published by The Council of American Ambassadors. The Council of American Ambassadors is a nonprofit, nonpartisan association of more than 200 former and incumbent non-career United States ambassadors that supports the role of the American ambassador and the country team in carrying out U.S. foreign policy at embassies around the world. In this connection, it provides advice and assistance to the U.S. Department of State, as appropriate, and endeavors to educate the public on foreign policy issues affecting the national interest.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.americanambassadors.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>589</id>
		<name>University of Denver - Graduate School of International Studies</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.du.edu/gsis/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>590</id>
		<name>Finnish Institute of International Affairs</name>
		<blurb>The Finnish Institute of International Affairs (FIIA) is an independent research institute that functions in association with the Parliament of Finland. The mission of the Finnish Institute of International Affairs is to conduct and publish research on international political and economic affairs, as well as on issues relating to the European Union.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.upi-fiia.fi/fin/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>591</id>
		<name>Institute for Development and Peace</name>
		<blurb>The Institute for Development and Peace (&quot;Institut für Entwicklung und Frieden&quot; INEF) is operated by the Department of Philosophy and Social Sciences of the Gerhard Mercator University as a research institution providing scientific support for the Foundation for Development and Peace (&quot;Stiftung für Entwicklung und Frieden&quot; SEF). The Institute was founded in 1990 on the basis of a cooperation agreement between the Foundation for Development and Peace, initiated by the former chancellor Willy Brandt and the University of Duisburg. The goals of the Foundation and the Institute are: to investigate the interrelationships between development and peace, in particular in the Third World; to elucidate global interdependencies linking security, economy and ecology; to stimulate the national and international dialogue on global interdependencies and trends; to generate impulses for political action based on global responsibility in North and South, East and West; to provide public information and education on global trends and global governance.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.inef.de/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>592</id>
		<name>CONfines de Relaciones Internacionales y Ciencia Política</name>
		<blurb>CONfines de Relaciones Internacionales y Ciencia Política is a scholarly magazine that publishes investigative articles in the social sciences, specifically within the areas of political science and international relations.</blurb>
		<url>http://confines.mty.itesm.mx/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>593</id>
		<name>American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research</name>
		<blurb>The American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, founded in 1943, is dedicated to preserving and strengthening the foundations of freedom-limited government, private enterprise, vital cultural and political institutions, and a strong foreign policy and national defense-through scholarly research, open debate, and publications. AEI is located in Washington, D.C., and is one of America&#039;s largest and most respected &quot;think tanks.&quot; AEI research covers economics and trade; social welfare; government tax, spending, regulatory, and legal policies; U.S. politics; international affairs; and U.S. defense and foreign policies. The Institute publishes dozens of books and hundreds of articles and reports each year, and an influential policy magazine, The American Enterprise. AEI publications are distributed widely to government officials and legislators, business executives, journalists, and academics; its conferences, seminars, and lectures are regularly covered by national television.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.aei.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>600</id>
		<name>Asia-Pacific Research Center</name>
		<blurb>The Asia/Pacific Research Center (A/PARC) at Stanford University is dedicated to the study of key economic, political, and security issues in the region. A/PARC is comprised of Stanford faculty and graduate students working in close collaboration with scholars and distinguished leaders from the Asia Pacific region. The Center operates under the auspices of Stanford&#039;s Institute for International Studies, and its work is concentrated in three critical areas: research, education and training, and public outreach. The 85 faculty fellows and graduate students affiliated with A/PARC come from a diverse mix of disciplines-economics, political science, anthropology, history, engineering, chemistry, medicine, law, and business. This interdisciplinary expertise creates intellectual ferment and gives breadth and analytical depth to the Center&#039;s work on contemporary Asia. Many members of A/PARC&#039;s faculty have held high-level posts in government and business. With their extensive experiences in both the public and private sectors, the Center faculty bring mature judgment and practical insight to bear on issues of strategic concern.</blurb>
		<url>http://aparc.stanford.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>601</id>
		<name>Africa Policy Information Center</name>
		<blurb>The Africa Policy Information Center provides accessible information and analysis in order to promote U.S. and international policies toward Africa that advance economic, political and social justice and the full spectrum of human rights. APIC promotes citizen action to influence public policy through: disseminating information and analysis electronically and through publications that educate, frame policy debates, and promote a rich content of excluded progressive and African voices promoting dialogue and debates; and facilitating collaborative relationships through coalitions and networks.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.africapolicy.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>602</id>
		<name>Center on International Cooperation</name>
		<blurb>The Center on International Cooperation (CIC), an independent institute established at New York University in 1996, promotes policy research and international consultations on multilateral responses to transnational problems. Working with officials of government and intergovernmental agencies, as well as corporate and civil society leaders, the Center seeks to clarify the economic, political, legal and institutional foundations of effective international cooperation. It focuses on such diverse sectors as international justice, humanitarian assistance, development aid and international health. The Center&#039;s international and multidisciplinary staff Assess current needs and financing sources and, as necessary, explore the appropriateness and feasibility of alternative sources of funding and institutional arrangements. We intend these efforts to produce practical policy recommendations and help to increase the public understanding necessary to implement and sustain essential multilateral activities.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cic.nyu.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>603</id>
		<name>Center for Defense Information</name>
		<blurb>Founded in 1972 as an independent monitor of the U.S. military, the Center for Defense Information is a private, nongovernmental, research organization. Its directors and staff believe that strong social, economic, political, and military components and a healthy environment contribute equally to the nation&#039;s security. CDI seeks realistic and cost-effective military spending without excess expenditures for weapons and policies that increase the danger of war. CDI supports adequate defense by evaluating our defense needs and how best to meet them without wasteful spending or compromising national security.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cdi.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>604</id>
		<name>Centre for European Policy Studies</name>
		<blurb>Centre for European Policy Studies (CEPS) is the leading &quot;think tank&quot; on European affairs. Based in Brussels, its strong team of analysts and researchers unearth the facts, provide the ideas and suggest policy alternatives on a wide range of European Union issues. CEPS&#039; independent position enables it to criticise and to stimulate debate. Its international network of members and associates in business, government, interest groups and academia acts as a source of information and ideas and a sounding board for new proposals. CEPS Possesses the capacity to anticipate trends and developments well before they are common knowledge and gives its members an opportunity to prepare their own positions and influence policy choices. Since its founding in 1982, CEPS&#039; policy papers and working parties on EMU, CAP reform, fiscal policy, institutional reform, and enlargement have contributed ideas that have been adopted by the policy makers in the Commission, the Council and the European Parliament and in the governments of the member states. CEPS obtains its core income from membership fees, programmes and rather less than 10% from official government grants including that from the EU.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ceps.be/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>605</id>
		<name>Pugwash Conferences on Science and World Affairs</name>
		<blurb>The purpose of the Pugwash Conferences is to bring together, from around the world, influential scholars and public figures concerned with reducing the danger of armed conflict and seeking cooperative solutions for global problems. Meeting in private as individuals, rather than as representatives of governments or institutions, Pugwash participants exchange views and explore alternative approaches to arms control and tension reduction with a combination of candor, continuity, and flexibility seldom attained in official East-West and North-South discussions and negotiations. Yet, because of the stature of many of the Pugwash participants in their own countries (as, for example, science and arms-control advisers to governments, key figures in academies of science and universities, and former and future holders of high government office), insights from Pugwash discussions tend to penetrate quickly to the appropriate levels of official policy-making.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.pugwash.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>606</id>
		<name>George C. Marshall European Center for Security Studies</name>
		<blurb>The mission of the Marshall Center is to create a more stable security environment by advancing democratic institutions and relationships, especially in the field of defense; promoting active, peaceful security cooperation; and enhancing enduring partnerships among the nations of North America, Europe and Eurasia. The legacy, goals, and ideals of the Marshall Plan continue through the security education initiatives of the George C. Marshall European Center for Security Studies. The Marshall Center is a renowned international educational institution that promotes dialogue and understanding among the nations of North America, Europe and Eurasia. Dedicated in 1993, the Marshall Center&#039;s mission is to continue Marshall&#039;s vision in the 21st Century. Supported bilaterally by the governments of the United States and Germany, the Marshall Center boasts an international staff and faculty, and is distinct from NATO institutions. The Marshall Center&#039;s College of International and Security Studies (CISS) and Conference Center conduct a variety of unique programs to date officials from 62 countries. All programs are taught in three languages: English, German and Russian. The CISS maintains a long-term academic focus while the Conference Center focuses on current issues and problem solving.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.marshallcenter.org</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>607</id>
		<name>Institute for National Strategic Studies</name>
		<blurb>The Institute for National Strategic Studies (INSS) is a policy research and strategic gaming organization within the National Defense University serving the U.S. Department of Defense, its components, and interagency partners. The Institute provides timely, objective analysis and gaming events to senior decision makers and supports NDU educational programs in the fields of international security and defense policy. Through an active outreach program, including conferences, international exchanges, and publications, the Institute seeks to promote wider understanding of emerging international security challenges and defense policy options. Established by the Secretary of Defense in 1984, INSS is comprised of four components: the Research Directorate, which analyzes global and regional security trends and frames national security policy and defense strategy options for senior decision-makers; the National Strategic Gaming Center, which develops and facilitates numerous strategic-level policy exercises and experiential learning activities for senior Executive Branch officials, the military combatant commands, Members of Congress, and various NDU educational programs; the Conference Directorate, which annually organizes several major symposia and supports more than 100 other conferences, seminars, and round-tables organized by the research staff; and NDU Press, which is responsible for the editorial development and production of a range of NDU publications, as well as Joint Force Quarterly, published for the Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff. The Strategic Forum provides summaries of work by members and guests of the Institute for National Strategic Studies and the National Defense University faculty. These include reports of original research, synopses of seminars and conferences, the results of unclassified war games, and digests of remarks by distinguished speakers. The McNair Papers are published at Fort Lesley J. McNair, home of the Institute for National Strategic Studies and the National Defense University. An Army post since 1794, the fort was given its present name in 1948 in honor of Lieutenant General Lesley James McNair. General McNair, known as &quot;Educator of the Army&quot; and trainer of some three million troops, was about to take command of Allied ground forces in Europe under Eisenhower, whence was killed in combat in Normandy, 25 July 1944. For information on availability of specific titles, in hard copy, contact NDU Press, Attn: NDU-NSS-PD, 300 5th Avenue, Fort Lesley J. McNair, Washington, DC 20319-5066 (telephone: (202) 685-4210).</blurb>
		<url>http://inss.dodlive.mil/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>608</id>
		<name>The Brookings Institution</name>
		<blurb>A private, independent, nonprofit research organization, Brookings seeks to improve the performance of American institutions, the effectiveness of government programs, and the quality of U.S. public policies. It addresses current and emerging policy challenges and offers practical recommendations for dealing with them, expressed in language that is accessible to policy makers and the general public alike. In its research, The Brookings Institution functions as an independent analyst and critic, committed to publishing its findings for the information of the public. In its conferences and activities, it serves as a bridge between scholarship and public policy bringing new knowledge to the attention of decision makers and affording scholars a better insight into public policy issues. The Institution traces its beginnings to 1916 with the founding of the Institute for Government Research, the first private organization devoted to public policy issues at the national level. In 1922 and 1924, the Institute was joined by two supporting sister organizations, the Institute of Economics and the Robert Brookings Graduate School. In 1927, these three groups were consolidated into one institution, named in honor of Robert Somers Brookings (1850-1932), a St. Louis businessman whose leadership shaped the earlier organizations. Brookings is financed largely by endowment and by the support of philanthropic foundations, corporations, and private individuals. Its funds are devoted to carrying out its own research and educational activities. It also undertakes some unclassified government contract studies, reserving the right to publish its findings.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.brookings.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>609</id>
		<name>EastWest Institute</name>
		<blurb>The East West Institute&#039;s mission is to defuse tensions and conflicts that threaten geopolitical stability while building democracy, free enterprise and prosperity in Central and Eastern Europe, Russia and other states of Eurasia. The Institute&#039;s resources and strengths. Insight gained from vast experience since its founding in 1981. A global network of relationships, based on shared values, with leaders in the business, governmental, non-governmental and intellectual communities. The objectivity and flexibility of a fiercely independent, not-for-profit organization. Dedication to providing international assistance to regional leadership to address critical issues at both the local and global levels. A determined commitment to act and to produce results.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ewi.info/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>610</id>
		<name>Center for International Security and Cooperation</name>
		<blurb>The Center for International Security and Cooperation, part of Stanford University&#039;s Institute for International Studies, is a multidisciplinary community dedicated to research and training in the field of international security. The Center brings together scholars, policymakers, scientists, area specialists, members of the business community, and other experts to examine a wide range of international security issues. CISAC publishes its own series of reports and papers on its work and also sponsors a series, Studies in International Security and Arms Control, through Stanford University Press.</blurb>
		<url>http://cisac.stanford.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>611</id>
		<name>Human Rights  Human Welfare (University of Denver)</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.du.edu/gsis/hrhw/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>612</id>
		<name>Center for the Advanced Study of India</name>
		<blurb>CASI&#039;s purpose is to link American and Indian academics, policymakers and professionals through interdisciplinary and collaborative programs focused on aspects of modern India. Cooperation between departments, professional schools and research centers at Penn, other universities in the United States and comparable institutions in India are facilitating joint research in broad fields of inquiry. These include international security, economic development, governance in multicultural societies, global communications, energy and the environment. CASI was officially inaugurated at Penn on June, 1992, with the help of grants from the Ford Foundation and the Ministry of External Affairs of the Government of India.</blurb>
		<url>http://casi.ssc.upenn.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>613</id>
		<name>Minda de Gunzburg Center for European Studies, Harvard University</name>
		<blurb>The Minda de Gunzburg Center for European Studies at Harvard University supports Harvard and M.I.T. graduate student dissertation research, hosts European academics and public figures, organizes conferences and workshops, encourages individual and group research, and conducts sixteen study groups. Center associates have followed such issues as the transitions in Eastern Europe, the renewed appeals of nationalism and religion, the formal structuring of the European Union, the evolving aspects of gender, new concepts of citizenship, as well as long-term historical change. CES Working Papers Series: Edited by Andrew Martin, the CES Working Papers Series reflects the interdiscipinary nature of the Center for European Studies at Harvard University. Papers written by affiliates of the Center or presented at study groups  conferences at CES range in topic from economics and political science to sociology and culture. European issues are looked at from both comparative  historical perspectives.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ces.fas.harvard.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>614</id>
		<name>The Fletcher School, Tufts University</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://fletcher.tufts.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>615</id>
		<name>Max Planck Institute for the Study of Societies</name>
		<blurb>The Max Planck Institute for the Study of Societies, a member institute of the Max Planck Society, is devoted to basic research in the social sciences. Its work focuses on the governance of advanced industrial societies in the face of internationalization and economic globalization, in particular on the changing roles and capacities of states and other corporate actors under conditions of international interdependence and supranational integration. From the analytical perspective of an actor-centered institutionalism, projects at the institute assess multilevel and multi-actor processes of decision making, negotiation and coordination, and apply theory modules of evolutionary dynamics as well as political economy. Devoted to international cooperation as the most promising organizational form of comparative research, the Institute gladly welcomes visitors doing research within its area of interest, whom it tries to provide with a working environment that is both productive and pleasant.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.mpi-fg-koeln.mpg.de/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>618</id>
		<name>Critical Review Foundation</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.criticalreview.com/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>619</id>
		<name>Conference Group on French Politics  Society</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url></url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>620</id>
		<name>U.S. Government</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.usa.gov/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>621</id>
		<name>The Strategic Studies Institute of the U.S. Army War College</name>
		<blurb>The Strategic Studies Institute of the US Army War College publishes security and strategic reports and publications which serve to influence policy debate and bridge the gap between Military and Academia. Their products are available at no cost.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.strategicstudiesinstitute.army.mil/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>622</id>
		<name>European Union Institute for Security Studies</name>
		<blurb>The European Union Institute for Security Studies (EUISS) is a Paris-based agency of the European Union, operating under the EU&#039;s second pillar, the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP). Its goals are to find a common security culture for the EU, to help develop and project the CFSP, and to enrich Europe&#039;s strategic debate.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.iss.europa.eu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>625</id>
		<name>The Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars</name>
		<blurb>The Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars is a presidential memorial that fosters scholarship and dialogue in the humanities and the social sciences. By bringing Fellows from around the world to Washington, D.C., encouraging discourse among disciplines and professions, and publishing the results of these activities, the Center enriches the quality of knowledge and debate in the nation&#039;s capital and throughout the world. The Woodrow Wilson Center was established by legislation in 1968 to symbolize and strengthen &quot;the fruitful relation between the world of learning and the world of public affairs.&quot; Created within the Smithsonian Institution, the Center has an independent Board of Trustees and administration. The Wilson Council is a group of private citizens who advise and support the Center. Funding for the Center comes from annual federal appropriations, private gifts and grants, and endowment income.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.wilsoncenter.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>626</id>
		<name>The Washington Institute for Near East Policy</name>
		<blurb>Founded in 1985, The Washington Institute for Near East Policy is a public educational foundation dedicated to scholarly research and informed debate on U.S. interests in the Middle East. Through a comprehensive program of research, seminars, conferences, publications, and study tours to the Middle East, The Washington Institute provides policymakers, diplomats, and journalists with fresh thinking and new ideas to promote peace, security, and stability in one of the world&#039;s most volatile regions.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.washingtoninstitute.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>627</id>
		<name>United States Institute of Peace</name>
		<blurb>The United States Institute of Peace is an independent, nonpartisan, national institution established and funded by Congress. Its goals are to help: Prevent and resolve violent international conflicts Promote post-conflict stability and development Increase conflict management capacity, tools, and intellectual capital worldwide. The Institute does this by empowering others with knowledge, skills, and resources, as well as by directly engaging in peace building efforts around the globe.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.usip.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>628</id>
		<name>Norwegian Institute of International Affairs</name>
		<blurb>The Norwegian Institute of International Affairs (NUPI) was established by the Norwegian Parliament in 1959 in order to promote a better understanding of international issues in Norway. NUPI has sought to achieve this by undertaking a wide range of research activities and by disseminating information on international issues. The Institute has an independent position in studying matters of relevance to Norwegian foreign policy and economic relations. As a small nation, Norway depends strongly on stable and open ties to the rest of the world. Consequently, the understanding of international relations and the constantly evolving international economy is a vital prerequisite when the foreign, as well as domestic policy of Norway is to be shaped. With more than 40 years of experience, NUPI is one of Norway&#039;s leading independent centres for research and information on political and economic issues.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.nupi.no/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>629</id>
		<name>The Combating Terrorism Center at West Point</name>
		<blurb>The Combating Terrorism Center at West Point contributes relevant scholarly perspectives through education, research and policy analysis to combat terrorist threats to the United States. We maintain expertise in four primary areas: terrorism, counterterrorism, homeland security, and weapons of mass destruction. By developing a curriculum of the highest quality, producing theoretically informed studies, and crafting relevant policy recommendations, we remain an internationally recognized center of excellence dedicated to the advancement of terrorism knowledge and expertise.</blurb>
		<url>http://ctc.usma.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>630</id>
		<name>Kellogg Institute for International Studies</name>
		<blurb>The Kellogg Institute for International Studies is designed to advance understanding of Third World development, particularly in Latin America, through research, education, and outreach. In its study of Latin America and other developing areas, the Institute focuses primarily on democratization and the quality of democracy; paths to development; religion and the Catholic Church; social movements and organized civil society; and public policies for social justice.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.nd.edu/~kellogg/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>633</id>
		<name>Romanian Academic Society</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.sar.org.ro/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>634</id>
		<name>East View Press</name>
		<blurb>East View Press is the journal and book publishing division of East View Information Services and its related company, East View Geospatial. Currently, East View Press is the publisher of six periodicals and the exclusive distributor of two periodicals geared toward serving researchers and others interested in major international and public policy questions, especially as they relate to the geographic area of the former Soviet Union and China.
</blurb>
		<url>http://www.eastview.com/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>635</id>
		<name>The Carter Center</name>
		<blurb>The Carter Center in Atlanta, Georgia, is a nonprofit, nonpartisan public policy institute founded by former U.S. President Jimmy Carter and his wife, Rosalynn, in 1982. The Center is dedicated to fighting disease, hunger, poverty, conflict, and oppression through collaborative initiatives in the areas of democratization and development, global health, and urban revitalization. At present, the Center operates 13 core programs, which have touched the lives of people in 65 countries, including the United States. The Center is a separately chartered and independently governed member of the Emory University community. Carter Center programs are directed by resident experts, many of whom hold academic appointments at Emory University.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cartercenter.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>636</id>
		<name>International Security Information Service</name>
		<blurb>The International Security Information Service (ISIS) was founded in 1989 in London to provide factual information and analysis on issues of international defence and security to parliamentarians and other interested parties. Its primary purpose has been to improve the level of understanding of these complex issues, enhance the quality of parliamentary debate in particular, and hence to help to hold the British Government to account for its foreign and defence policies. In August 1995, ISIS expanded its operation to Brussels where it established a parallel organisation, ISIS Europe, to provide a similar service to a wider European audience. ISIS Europe aim to improve the quality and range of defence and security issues discussed within and between the institutions with competencies in foreign affairs and security policy in Brussels and, increasingly, in other western and eastern European national parliaments. One of the principal means which ISIS adopts to inform and influence parliamentarians is the publication of briefing papers. These briefings and reports are prepared by experts from material collected from public sources. They are freely and openly available to politicians, civil servants, journalists and others interested in this area of public affairs. Since it was established in September 1995, ISIS Europe has published eighteen such briefings and eleven shorter briefings on developments in the Intergovernmental Conference (IGC) negotiations to amend the Maastricht Treaty. ISIS Europe&#039;s specialist reports are customised for, and targeted at, key individuals and committees within the UK and many European parliaments. In order to maximise the impact of its analysis, ISIS employs methods that ensure the material is read by the right person at the most appropriate time. This requires good analytical judgement, personal contact and a trusted relationship with its clientele, and a thorough knowledge of legislative procedures and agendas. Over the past year ISIS Europe has sought to develop its contacts in central and eastern European parliaments. It is on the basis of this experience that ISIS Europe is now engaged in a research project which examines the role of the parliaments of Central and Eastern European states in influencing and scrutinising foreign and defence policy. ISIS Europe also engages actively in the work of the European Parliament, acting as a consultancy service to many of its Members and co-ordinating inter-party support for specific initiatives in the field of defence and security. For example it co-ordinates fortnightly inter-party meetings to discuss current legislative initiatives and monthly meetings of the Parliament&#039;s Arms Transfers Working Group. This group aims to influence the process of developing stricter European arms export controls and explores ways in which the EU can address the issues of surplus light weapons, illicit trafficking in conventional arms, and the furtherance &#039;of security first&#039; development assistance policies.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.isis-europe.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>637</id>
		<name>American Assembly at Columbia University</name>
		<blurb>The American Assembly, an affiliate of Columbia University, was founded by President Dwight D. Eisenhower in 1950 &quot;to illuminate issues of public policy&quot;. The Assembly&#039;s major objectives are: to focus attention and stimulate informed discussion on a range of critical U.S. policy topics, both domestic and international; to inform government officials, community and civic leadership, and the general public regarding the factual background and the range of policy options in a given issue; to facilitate increased communication among decision makers from the public and private sectors, as well as from institutions and organizations concerned with critical public policy issues; and to raise on a continuing basis the level and quality of public policy discourse on national and international issues.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.americanassembly.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>641</id>
		<name>U.S. Military Academy, Department of Social Science</name>
		<blurb>The Department of Social Sciences of the United States Military Academy is the focal point for political science and economics education at West Point. The department has a large faculty composed of both military officers and civilian academics engaged in research on a wide range of topics relevant to international affairs. The views expressed in these papers are those of the authors and do not reflect the official policy or position of the United States Military Academy, the Department of the Army, or the Department of Defense or U.S. Government.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.usma.edu/sosh/SitePages/Home.aspx</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>642</id>
		<name>Asia Society</name>
		<blurb>The Asia Society is America&#039;s leading institution dedicated to fostering understanding of Asia and communication between Americans and the peoples of Asia and the Pacific. Through art exhibitions and performances, films, lectures, seminars and conferences, publications and assistance to the media, and materials and programs for students and teachers, the Asia Society presents the uniqueness and diversity of Asia to the American people. Founded in 1956 by John D. Rockefeller 3rd, the Society reaches audiences around the United States through its headquarters in New York and regional centers in Houston, Los Angeles, San Francisco and Washington, DC. Asians from all walks of life also participate in the Society&#039;s work through its regional centers in Hong Kong, Manila, Melbourne and Shanghai, an International Council, and programs in Asia. A national nonprofit, nonpartisan educational organization, the Society provides a forum for building awareness of the more than thirty countries broadly defined as the Asia-Pacific region - the area from Japan to Iran, and from Central Asia to New Zealand, Australia and the Pacific Islands. The Asia Society is supported by contributions from foundations, corporations, and individuals who believe in the mandate of the Society: to build bridges of understanding between Americans and Asians.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.asiasociety.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>643</id>
		<name>Aspen Institute</name>
		<blurb>The Aspen Institute is an international nonprofit educational institution dedicated to enhancing the quality of leadership through informed dialogue. It convenes men and women who represent diverse viewpoints and backgrounds from business, labor, government, the professions, the arts, and the nonprofit sector to relate timeless ideas and values to the foremost challenges facing societies, organizations, and individuals.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.aspeninstitute.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>644</id>
		<name>S.Rajaratnam School of International Studies</name>
		<blurb>The Institute of Defence and Strategic Studies (IDSS) at Nanyang Technological University (NTU) was established on 30 July 1996 by Dr Tony Tan Keng Yam, then Deputy Prime Minister and Minister for Defence. On 1 January 2007, ten years after its establishment, IDSS was formally inaugurated to become the S. Rajaratnam School of International Studies (RSIS). In the new School, IDSS remains as a key component Institute focusing on security research to serve national needs while the School would take over its teaching functions. Since its establishment, the School has acquired the reputation as a leading research and graduate teaching institution in strategic and international affairs in the Asia-Pacific region. RSIS will bring IDSS and NTU to the next level besides enhancing Singapore&#039;s standing as a regional and international hub for higher education and research. IDSS&#039; new name also serves to honour the contributions of the late Mr. S. Rajaratnam who held various Cabinet appointments until his retirement. He was also one of Singapore&#039;s founding fathers and well respected as a visionary diplomat and strategic thinker.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.rsis.edu.sg/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>646</id>
		<name>Center for German and European Studies, University of California, Berkeley</name>
		<blurb>The University of California Center for German and European Studies has launched a major research initiative, which includes scholars from throughout the UC system, the United States, and abroad. The research sponsored by the Center is organized around four principal themes: Political Economy of European Integration European Political and Social Cultures European Political Relations and Institutions European Socioeconomic Integration The Center has established a Working Paper series to make the results of this research immediately available and to circulate work in progress prior to its final publication. In addition to the research of these established study groups, the Working Papers include specially selected papers from conferences, workshops, and public lectures that have been presented by the Center.</blurb>
		<url>http://ies.berkeley.edu/cgs/index.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>647</id>
		<name>Oxfam Publishing</name>
		<blurb>Oxfam GB publishes and distributes a range of books, journals, reports, training resources, videos and policy papers. Through its publishing, Oxfam sets out to communicate its policy research, advocacy messages, and programme experience, and to be an active contributor to current debates in development.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.oxfam.org.uk/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>649</id>
		<name>Watson Institute for International Studies, Brown University</name>
		<blurb>Brown University&#039;s Watson Institute for International Studies evolved from Thomas J. Watson Jr.&#039;s (class of 1937) vision for a research and teaching center that would address the most pressing problems of its time. The Watson Institute&#039;s mission and scope today include support of multidisciplinary research, teaching, and public education on international affairs. The Institute promotes the work of students, faculty, visiting scholars, and policy practitioners who analyze and develop initiatives to address contemporary global problems.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.watsoninstitute.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>661</id>
		<name>Institute on Global Conflict and Cooperation, University of California</name>
		<blurb>The University of California Institute on Global Conflict and Cooperation (IGCC) was founded in 1983 as a multicampus research unit serving the entire University of California (UC) system. The institute&#039;s purpose is to study the causes of international conflict and the opportunities to resolve it through international cooperation. During IGCC&#039;s first five years, research focused largely on the issue of averting nuclear war through arms control and confidence-building measures between the superpowers. Since then the research program has diversified to encompass several broad areas of inquiry: regional relations, international environmental policy, international relations theory, and most recently the domestic sources of foreign policy. IGCC serves as a liaison between the academic and policy communities, injecting fresh ideas into the policy process, establishing the intellectual foundations for effective policy-making in the post-Cold War environment, and providing opportunities and incentives for UC faculty and students to become involved in international policy debates. Scholars, researchers, government officials, and journalists from the United States and abroad participate in all IGCC projects, and IGCC&#039;s publications-books, policy papers, and a semiannual newsletter-are widely distributed to individuals and institutions around the world.</blurb>
		<url>http://igcc.ucsd.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>672</id>
		<name>Berkeley Roundtable on the International Economy</name>
		<blurb>The Berkeley Roundtable on the International Economy (BRIE) is a small, interdisciplinary research project at the University of California at Berkeley. For nearly fifteen years, BRIE has worked with academics, business leaders, and scholars from around the world from such wide-ranging disciplines as urban planning, political science, economics, and engineering to consider the real-world interactions of technology, markets, and economies and to formulate path-breaking positions that challenge conventional economic policy-making. BRIE stands today as one of the leading intellectual voices debating government policy and business strategy.</blurb>
		<url>http://brie.berkeley.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>676</id>
		<name>Carnegie Commission on Preventing Deadly Conflict</name>
		<blurb>The Carnegie Corporation of New York established the Carnegie Commission on Preventing Deadly Conflict in May 1994 to address the looming threats to world peace of intergroup violence and to advance new ideas for the prevention and resolution of deadly conflict. The Commission has examined the principal causes of deadly ethnic, nationalist, and religious conflicts within and between states and the circumstances that foster or deter their outbreak. Taking a long-term, worldwide view of violent conflicts that are likely to emerge, it seeks to determine the functional requirements of an effective system for preventing mass violence and to identify the ways in which such a system could be implemented. The Commission looks at the strengths and weaknesses of various international entities in conflict prevention and considers ways in which international organizations might contribute toward developing an effective international system of nonviolent problem solving.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.wilsoncenter.org/subsites/ccpdc/index.htm</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>681</id>
		<name>Center for Global Security and Democracy</name>
		<blurb>The Center for Global Security and Democracy, comprised of faculty, students, independent scholars, activists, information technologists and members of the community, exists to produce and propagate the knowledge and skills necessary to build a more secure and democratic world. In collaboration with universities, NGOs, citizensâ groups, local and national governments, and corporate partners, CGSD harnesses the resources of Rutgers and the community to promote informed action and to create the open, democratic Internet information and networking infrastructure required for global collaboration.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cgsd.rutgers.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>684</id>
		<name>Center for International Studies, University of Southern California</name>
		<blurb>The Center for International Studies (CIS) at the University of Southern California was established in 1986 by the USC School of International Relations to promote advanced research and sustained discussion of theoretical and policy issues in international political and economic affairs. The Center supports the research of faculty, students and CIS members, hosts scholars from the United States and abroad, organizes public seminars, sponsors workshops and conferences and promotes collaborative research intended to promote a broader understanding of international affairs. Past directors have included Thomas Biersteker, John S. Odell, Abraham Lowenthal and Laurie Brand. The current director is Peter Rosendorff.</blurb>
		<url>http://usccis.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>687</id>
		<name>Center for Muslim-Christian Understanding</name>
		<blurb>The Center for Muslim-Christian Understanding: History and International Affairs was established in 1993 by Georgetown University and the Fondation pour l&#039;Entente entre Chrétiens et Musulmans, Geneva, to foster the study of Muslim-Christian relations and to promote dialogue between practictioners of the two great religions. The Center focuses on the historical, theological, political and cultural encounter of Islam and Christianity, the Muslim world and the West. Located in the Edmund A. Walsh School of Foreign Service at Georgetown University, the Center combines teaching, research and public affairs activities.</blurb>
		<url>http://cmcu.georgetown.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>689</id>
		<name>Center for Studies of Social Change</name>
		<blurb>The Center for Studies of Social Change (CSSC) was founded by Charles Tilly in 1984, when he joined the Graduate Faculty, New School for Social Research as Distinguished Professor of Sociology and History. The CSSC was modelled after the Center for Research in Social Organization at the University of Michigan, which Tilly had headed for many years. Projected as the research complement to the Committee on Historical Studies, the CSSC has since 1984 supported research on large-scale change, and provided a setting in which faculty and students in Historical Studies have pursued their own investigations. CSSC has also served as a center for the exchange of ideas, materials, and personnel from Asis, Europe, and Latin America through its partial support for several visiting research associates per academic year.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.newschool.edu/gf/centers/gf_cssc.htm</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>691</id>
		<name>Centre d&#039;Etudes et de Recherches Internationales</name>
		<blurb>The CERI, founded in 1952, within the Fondation Nationale des Sciences Politiques (FNSP), is France&#039;s foremost center for research on the international political system. As a joint FNSP-CNRS research unit, the CERI is made up of some sixty researchers and about fifteen support staff who handle financial management, documentation, publications and communication. The CERI&#039;s mission is to bring together area studies specialists and international relations experts. It analyzes the contemporary political world, with a strong emphasis on an interdisciplinary approach: its research fellows include not only political scientists but also economists, sociologists, historians and anthropologists. The CERI has a twofold objective: to contribute to an in-depth understanding of political societies abroad and the dynamics of the world system; to provide expert analysis on today&#039;s major international issues. Its topics of study are issues central to international relations research, including: globalization, forms of regional integration - particularly the building of the European Union - new forms of conflict, democratization, migrations, nationalism and other political identities. Its relations with the international scientific community are essential to the CERI&#039;s research activity: hosting foreign scholars, participating in international programs, attending major world conferences. The Russia Papers are published by the Center for International Studies and Research (CERI) at Sciences Po University in Paris. The Editor is Marie Mendras. The series offers original analyses on Russia in the fields of internal politics, economic affairs, demographic and social issues, culture and identity, and foreign policy. In a comparative and regional perspective, The Russia Papers are open to studies on other former Soviet republics.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ceri-sciencespo.com/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>693</id>
		<name>Center for Transatlantic Relations</name>
		<blurb>The SAIS Center for Transatlantic Relations, located near Dupont Circle in Washington, DC, engages international scholars and students directly with government officials, journalists, business executives, and other opinion leaders from both sides of the Atlantic on issues facing Europe and North America. Center activities include seminars and lectures; media programs and web-based activities; research projects and policy study groups.</blurb>
		<url>http://transatlantic.sais-jhu.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>695</id>
		<name>Centre for International Governance Innovation</name>
		<blurb>CIGI was founded to develop solutions for some of the world&#039;s most pressing international governance challenges through world-class research. CIGI strives to find and develop ideas for global change by studying, advising and networking with scholars, practitioners and governments on the character and desired reforms of multilateral governance. Through conferences, publications, public events and technology CIGI aims to raise the Canadian domestic capacity to effect change in public policy in Canada and around the world.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cigionline.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>696</id>
		<name>Global Facilitation Network for Security Sector Reform</name>
		<blurb>The Global Facilitation Network for Security Sector Reform (GFN-SSR) is a project funded by the UK Government&#039;s Global Conflict Prevention Pool (GCPP) and is managed by a team of academics and practitioners at Cranfield University&#039;s Shrivenham campus. The team serves as a resource for the UK Government as well as other global institutional, organisational, and government partners to provide research that facilitates policy development and capacity building for global Security Sector Reform initiatives.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ssrnetwork.net/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>697</id>
		<name>Centre for the Study of Democracy, University of Westminster</name>
		<blurb>The Centre for the Study of Democracy (CSD) is the postgraduate and postdoctoral research center in Politics and International Relations at the University of Westminster. CSD offers a one-year, full-time M.A. in International Relations and Political Theory, an M.Phil. and a Ph.D. Rising domestic and international academic and media interest in the work of CSD has ensured its reputation as a center of original and excellent research unlike any other in Britain. CSD&#039;s achievements were recognized in the recent national HEFCE Research Assessment Exercise (1996) with a 3A Research Rating placing CSD at the joint top of the New University Ratings in Politics and International Relations.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.wmin.ac.uk/sshl/page-1</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>700</id>
		<name>Centre for the Study of Terrorism and Political Violence, St. Andrews University, Scotland</name>
		<blurb>The center is concerned not only with the study of terrorism and related forms of political violence, but also with other nontraditional modes of international conflict including various manifestations of intercommunal ethnic strife, multinational peacekeeping and peace enforcement, and the grey area between political conflict and criminal activity. Its major goals are to investigate the roots of political violence; develop a body of theory spanning its various and disparate elements; and recommend policy and organizational initiatives that the government and private sectors might adopt to better predict, detect, and respond to the threats and challenges of the post-cold war era. The centre&#039;s work is largely facilitated through its possession and amalgamation of two of the world&#039;s pre-eminent database sources on terrorism and political violence: The RAND-St. Andrews University Databases on Terrorism and Low-Intensity Conflict and the collection of materials on 20th century conflict donated by Control Risks Ltd. Both of these resources consist of newspaper clippings and journal articles from more than 100 countries and in 5 languages. In addition, material from The RAND-St. Andrews databases is also organised in 9 online, specialised computerised &quot;chronologies&quot;, where terrorist incidents and other acts of politically-motivated violence are listed in chronological format and coded for rapid data retrieval. The largest and best know of these is The RAND Chronology of International Terrorism. It contains information on international terrorist incidents since 1968 derived from the open literature (as are all the databases); newspapers, journals, published government reports and documents, radio broadcasts, and the foreign press. It provides a comprehensive, independent source of information with which trends in various aspects of terrorism can be analyzed. In response to the governmental, military, scholarly, and public need for such a resource, a Chronology of International Terrorism is published annually.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.st-andrews.ac.uk/~wwwir/research/cstpv/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>702</id>
		<name>Centro de Investigación y Docencia Económicas</name>
		<blurb>CIDE is a unique academic institution. A center of advanced knowledge located in Mexico City, CIDE is engaged in world class research and teaching in the social sciences. The Center fosters a community of learning, with a group of diverse and talented people that believe that knowledge can truly make a difference in the way we think and act upon the great economic, social and political issues of our times. CIDE is a non-profit, public organization. Independent intellectually and self-governing in all aspects of its academic life, premised on the idea of knowledge as one of society&#039;s most critical and empowering public goods. In a country where for long decades the distinction between &quot;public&quot; and &quot;governmental&quot; was porous and unclear, CIDE stands at the vanguard of a definition of &quot;public&quot; that goes beyond government. It embraces the idea of bringing a common &quot;public good&quot; to Mexican society as a while through its unique characteristics and capabilities.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cide.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>705</id>
		<name>Economist Intelligence Unit</name>
		<blurb>We are the research and analysis division of The Economist Group, the sister company to The Economist newspaper. Created in 1946, we have nearly 70 years&#039; experience in helping businesses, financial firms and governments to understand how the world is changing and how that creates opportunities to be seized and risks to be managed. A British company, we are intensely global. We service clients across the world from our 40 offices, our staff speak over 25 languages and we embrace foreign cultures with a passion. Other Resources from the EIU: CIAO Atlas.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.eiu.com/home.aspx</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>706</id>
		<name>Clarke Center at Dickinson College</name>
		<blurb>The Clarke Forum for Contemporary Issues, founded in 1994 with a generous gift from Trustee Henry Clarke, brings the unique strengths of an interdisciplinary liberal arts perspective to the critical examination of pressing contemporary issues. The Clarke Forum connects the students and faculty of Dickinson College and members of the broader community with scholars, practicing professionals and activists through the use of lectures, seminars, and conferences. By encouraging engagement with these visitors in ways that allow for dialogue and critical reflection, The Clarke Forum helps prepare students to become knowledgeable, productive, and intellectually active citizens and leaders. The Clarke Forum also provides a space where faculty from many perspectives can come together to discuss ideas and solutions to social problems. With events that are free and open to the public, The Clarke Forum is a vital part of the community, continually enhancing public awareness and understanding of critical contemporary issues. Students are involved in all aspects of Clarke Forum activities: designing, planning, producing and broadcasting programs. Much of the Forum&#039;s day-to-day program implementation is in the hands of its Student Project Managers. The Clarke Forum also sponsors a Student Partnership Program which encourages collaborative work between the Forum&#039;s Project Manager&#039;s and students at area high schools. Clarke Forum students mentor high school students by training them in web-based research, desktop publishing, and preparation of promotional materials. The Clarke Forum believes that knowledge and understanding are gained through critical reflection and the informed exchange of divergent ideas, and facilitates such dialogue across the disciplines.</blurb>
		<url>http://clarke.dickinson.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>712</id>
		<name>Prof. Bulent Aras</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url></url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>713</id>
		<name>The European Institute</name>
		<blurb>The European Institute is the leading Washington-based public-policy organization devoted to transatlantic affairs. It provides an independent forum for US and European government and corporate decision makers, officials from multilateral organizations, foreign and economic policy analysts, and expert journalists to exchange information, develop innovative policy options, and create new professional working relationships.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.europeaninstitute.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>714</id>
		<name>Institute on Globalization and the Human Condition, McMaster University</name>
		<blurb>The Institute on Globalization and the Human Condition was set up in January 1998 in order to give life to the University Senate&#039;s decision to make Globalization and the Human Condition a &quot;Strategic Area&quot; of research at McMaster University. In giving &quot;life&quot; to the Strategic Area, the Institute has concentrated its efforts on two tasks. First, we have sought to build an intellectual community of the researchers (both faculty and graduate students) at the University and elsewhere interested in globalization and the human condition. Second, we have set up an interdisciplinary M.A. Programme in Globalization Studies, which received its first cohort of students in September 2004. With these activities, we seek to expand research and knowledge about globalizing processes and how these come to bear upon our lives, our communities, and the plants, animals and environments in which we live.</blurb>
		<url>http://globalization.mcmaster.ca/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>715</id>
		<name>European Journal of International Law</name>
		<blurb>The EJIL was established in 1990 by a small group of scholars based at the European University Institute, the Universities of Florence, Munich and Paris II and the Michigan Law School. The Journal has grown since then in size, strength and reputation, but the Editor - original vision remains unchanged.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ejil.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>716</id>
		<name>Cornell University Peace Studies Program</name>
		<blurb>The Peace Studies Program is an interdisciplinary program devoted to research and teaching on the problems of war and peace, arms control and disarmament, and more generally, instances of collective violence. Founded in 1970 with the support of the University&#039;s Center for International Studies and the Program on Science, Technology and Society, the Program&#039;s focus has evolved with changes in the world. In addition to its long-standing attention to arms control issues, particularly nuclear proliferation, the Program is engaged in a conversation on the future of the international security agenda in the post-Cold-War World. The Program is distinguished by its thoroughly interdisciplinary character and its emphasis on long-term policy issues. Both are essential for the Program&#039;s objective of investigating the intellectual foundations of security and the preservation of peace.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.einaudi.cornell.edu/PeaceProgram/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>717</id>
		<name>Uluslararasi Iliskiler</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.uidergisi.com/index.php</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>718</id>
		<name>Urban Institute</name>
		<blurb>The Urban Institute investigates social and economic problems confronting the nation and analyzes efforts to solve these problems. The Institute seeks to increase Americans&#039;s awareness of important public choices and improve the formulation and implementation of government decisions. Much of its research is available to the public.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.urban.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>721</id>
		<name>German Politics and Society Journal</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://cges.georgetown.edu/gps.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>734</id>
		<name>Columbia International Affairs Online</name>
		<blurb>Columbia International Affairs Online (CIAO) is designed to be the most comprehensive source for theory and research in international affairs. It publishes a wide range of scholarship that includes working papers from university research institutes, occasional papers series from NGOs, foundation-funded research projects, and proceedings from conferences.</blurb>
		<url></url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>735</id>
		<name>The Conference Board</name>
		<blurb>The Conference Board is the world&#039;s leading business research and membership organization with 2,800 companies and other enterprises in 63 counties. A not-for-profit, non-advocacy organization that has been in business for over 80 years, The Conference Board provides timely research on management practices and economic trends and is the most frequently quoted private source of business information.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.conference-board.org/economics/bci/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>736</id>
		<name>Small Arms Survey</name>
		<blurb>The Small Arms Survey is an independent research project located at the Graduate Institute of International Studies, Geneva, Switzerland. It serves as the principal international source of public information on all aspects of small arms, and as a resource centre for governments, policy makers, researchers, and activists. The project has an international staff with expertise in security studies, political science, international public policy, law, economics, development studies, conflict resolution, and sociology. The staff work closely with a worldwide network of researchers and partners.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.smallarmssurvey.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>740</id>
		<name>Japan Institute of International Affairs</name>
		<blurb>The Japan Institute of International Affairs (JIIA) is a private, non-profit, and independent research organization that was founded in 1959 through the initiative of former Prime Minister Shigeru Yoshida.
Since its foundation, JIIA&#039;s activities have been based on the five basic goals stipulated in its charter. They are:
To foster the scientific study of international politics, economics and law.
To provide the means for examining and researching international affairs.
To promote the exchange of information, knowledge, and views on international affairs.
To encourage research of international affairs at universities in Japan.
To promote exchanges with universities and research institutes in other countries.
In order to accomplish the above-stated goals, JIIA organizes study groups on various regional and global issues relevant to the formulation of Japan&#039;s foreign policy; it organizes international conferences, symposiums and seminars in order to foster dialogue and exchange of opinions with overseas counterparts; it conducts joint research projects with other research organizations and with universities, both domestic and overseas; it invites foreign researchers to Japan and assists them with their research activities; and it issues a wide range of publications as a result of these activities.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.jiia.or.jp/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>741</id>
		<name>Institute for European Studies at Cornell University</name>
		<blurb>The Cornell University Institute for European Studies coordinates and promotes interaction among the faculty and students from the University&#039;s thirty-one departments and divisions that deal with European subjects. The focus is on the new Europe, including the member nations of the European Union as well as the former states of the Soviet bloc. In its pan-European focus, the Institute is unique among programs of its type in the leading U.S. research universities. Along with several other internationally recognized area studies programs at Cornell, the Institute is affiliated with the University&#039;s Mario Einaudi Center for International Studies.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.einaudi.cornell.edu/Europe</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>743</id>
		<name>East-West Center</name>
		<blurb>The U.S. Congress established the East-West Center in 1960 to foster mutual understanding and cooperation among the governments and peoples of the Asia Pacific region, including the United States. Funding for the Center comes from the U.S. government with additional support provided by private agencies, individuals, corporations, and Asian and Pacific governments.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.eastwestcenter.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>744</id>
		<name>Christopher H. Browne Center for International Politics, University of Pennsylvania</name>
		<blurb>The Christopher H. Browne Center for International Politics at the University of Pennsylvania supports a variety of entries, periodic &quot;great debates&quot; on important contemporary issues in world politics, conferences and research seminars, and publication of a working papers series. Penn&#039;s Center for International Politics (CIP) will also invite outstanding senior and junior scholars and experienced practitioners to participate as visiting or post-doctoral fellows.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.sas.upenn.edu/brownecip/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>745</id>
		<name>European Centre for Minority Issues</name>
		<blurb>The European Centre for Minority Issues (ECMI) advances majority-minority relations in the wider Europe through action, research and documentation. It supports the stabilization of areas of ethnopolitical tension and conflict, contributes to the strengthening of relevant legislation and best practices in governance and enhances the capacity of civil society actors and governments to engage with one another in a constructive and sustainable way.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ecmi.de/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>746</id>
		<name>Geneva Centre for the Democratic Control of Armed Forces</name>
		<blurb>Established in October 2000 on the initiative of the Swiss government, the Geneva Centre for the Democratic Control of Armed Forces (DCAF) encourages and supports States and non-State governed institutions in their efforts to strengthen democratic and civilian control of armed and security forces, and promotes security sector reform in accordance with democratic standards. The Centre collects information and undertakes research in order to identify problems, to gather experience from lessons learned, and to propose best practices in the field of democratic governance of the security sector. The Centre provides its expertise and support, through practical work programmes on the ground, to all interested parties, in particular governments, parliaments, military authorities, international organisations, non-governmental organisations, and academic circles. CAF is an international foundation under Swiss law. DCAF&#039;s Foundation Council is made up of 45 governments including Switzerland, 40 other Euro-Atlantic States, 3 African States, and the Canton of Geneva. The Council is headed by Ambassador Edouard Brunner, former Secretary of State of the Swiss Federal Department of Foreign Affairs DCAF&#039;s International Advisory Board is composed of a group of over 60 experts in the various fields of DCAF&#039;s activity. DCAF Staff is comprised of some 50 employees coming from about 30 different nationalities. The Centre is directed by Ambassador Dr Theodor H Winkler.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.dcaf.ch/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>747</id>
		<name>European Research Papers Archive</name>
		<blurb>The ERPA network was founded by the Harvard Jean Monnet Chair, Prof. J.H.H. Weiler; the directors of the Cologne Max Planck Institute for the Study of Societies, Prof. Fritz Scharpf and Prof. Wolfgang Streeck; Prof. Philip Alston (Academy of European Law) and Prof. Yves Mény (Robert Schuman Centre) of the European University Institute; and the editor of the European Integration online Papers (EIoP), Dr. Michael Nentwich. The editors of the founding series are members of the management board. In the meantime, a few further papers joined the network. ERPA&#039;s aim is to provide a common access point for the online working paper series of the participating institutions in order to help researchers in the field of European Integration studies searching the growing number of working papers now available in the internet. ERPA is confined to high quality series in order to guarantee high standards. The participating series editors achieve this high level of scholarship by different means: while the Max Planck Institute, and the Harvard Jean Monnet Chair practise high-level internal refereeing, the Robert Schuman Centre and the EIoP have a double-blind review process with two referees per paper. All further participating series subscribe to a similar high-quality policy.</blurb>
		<url>http://eiop.or.at/erpa/erpainfo.htm</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>748</id>
		<name>European Union Studies Center</name>
		<blurb>The European Union Studies Center (EUSC) was established in 1993 under the directorship of Hugo M. Kaufmann, Professor of Economics at Queens College and at the Graduate Center. The EUSC is dedicated to promoting research and debate on the diverse issues and challenges facing the European Union. The approach to the research and analysis is interdisciplinary; it includes political, economic, legal, social and cultural aspects of the Union as a whole, as well as relations between European Union member states, and the European Union&#039;s relationship to the rest of the world. The emphasis of the studies reflects developments in the EU, especially its transition to the single currency and the European Union&#039;s Defense Initiative (and its relation to NATO). In addition, the Center explores the challenges of the Union&#039;s enlargement through the accession of central and eastern European countries, and, finally, the grand visions of a future for Europe -- from Confederacy to Federation: Quo vadis Europa?</blurb>
		<url>http://www.euromatters.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>749</id>
		<name>Foreign Policy In Focus</name>
		<blurb>The Interhemispheric Resource Center (IRC) and the Institute for Policy Studies (IPS) have joined together to coordinate the publication of a series of policy briefs on foreign policy issues. Each brief offers policy recommendations for a more responsible and visionary U.S. foreign policy. The Foreign Policy In Focus project is reaching out to hundreds of foreign policy organizations and experts to make the best of foreign policy analysis available to policymakers and the public. Working together, we are creating a comprehensive and compelling new foreign policy agenda for the United States.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.foreignpolicy-infocus.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>750</id>
		<name>Fourth Freedom Forum</name>
		<blurb>The Fourth Freedom Forum is working to create a more civilized world based on the force of law rather than the law of force. We believe that economic power is greater than military might, and that the effective use of economic incentives and sanctions offers the greatest hope for creating a more secure and peaceful future. By combining carrots economic and political incentives, diplomatic engagement, and offers of trade, investment, and technology with sticks especially the use of &quot;smart&quot; sanctions such as targeted financial sanctions and arms embargoes the world community can prevent nuclear proliferation, eliminate weapons of mass destruction, and enforce civilized standards of behavior without resort to military violence.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.fourthfreedom.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>751</id>
		<name>The Geneva Centre for Security Policy</name>
		<blurb>The Geneva Centre for Security Policy (GCSP) is an international foundation, created under the framework of Swiss participation in the Partnership for Peace. The GCSP has three core missions: to provide expert training in international security policy for diplomats, military officers and civil servants from foreign and defence ministries; to define, contribute and advance research in international security studies and to organise conferences and seminars accordingly; and to foster cooperative networking with countries, institutions and experts working in this area. The Foundation Members include: Austria, the Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, France, the Federal Republic of Germany, Hungary, Italy, Latvia, Poland, Romania, the Russian Federation, the Slovak Republic, Sweden, Switzerland, Turkey, Ukraine, the United Kingdom, the United States of America and the Canton of Geneva.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.gcsp.ch/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>752</id>
		<name>Global Development and Environment Institute at Tufts University</name>
		<blurb>The Global Development And Environment Institute was founded in 1993 to combine the research and curricular development activities of two Tufts programs: the Program for Sustainable Change and Development in the School of Arts and Sciences, and the Center for Environmental and Resource Policy at The Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ase.tufts.edu/gdae/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>753</id>
		<name>Independent Institute</name>
		<blurb>The Independent Institute is a non-partisan, scholarly, public-policy research and educational organization that sponsors comprehensive studies of critical social, economic, legal, and environmental issues. Adhering to the highest standards of scholarly inquiry and pursued regardless of prevailing political or social biases, the resulting studies are published and widely distributed as books, The Independent Review (quarterly journal), and other publications, and are publicly debated through numerous conference and media programs. Through this uncommon independence, depth, and clarity, The Independent Institute pushes at the frontiers of our knowledge, redefines the debate over public issues, and fosters new and effective directions for government reform.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.independent.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>754</id>
		<name>Initiative on Conflict Resolution and Ethnicity</name>
		<blurb>Established in 1993, INCORE (International Conflict research) is a joint project of the United Nations University and the University of Ulster. Combining research, education and comparative analysis, INCORE addresses the causes and consequences of conflict in Northern Ireland and internationally and promotes conflict resolution management strategies. It aims to influence policymakers and practitioners involved in peace, conflict and reconciliation issues while enhancing the nature of international conflict research.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.incore.ulst.ac.uk/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>755</id>
		<name>Institute for Conflict Analysis and Resolution at George Mason University</name>
		<blurb>The Institute for Conflict Analysis and Resolution offers the Doctor of Philosophy (PhD) and the Master of Science (MS) degrees in Conflict Analysis and Resolution. Both degree programs are among the first in this field and are part of the mission of the Institute: to advance the understanding and resolution of significant and persistent social conflicts. Three additional components enhance the Institute&#039;s degree programs: research and publication, a clinical and consultancy program, and public education. Major research interests include the analysis of conflict between and within nations; ethnic, religious, and identity groups; organizations and social classes; the exploration of conditions attracting parties to the negotiation table; the role of third parties in dispute resolution; and the testing of a variety of conflict intervention methods in community, national, and international settings.A Clinical program is offered to students through the Applied Practice and Theory Program (two semesters), and through consultantcy work with individual Institute faculty, associates, and affiliate organizations. Community outreach is accomplished through the publication of books and articles, public lectures, conferences, seminars, and special briefings on the theory and practice of conflict resolution. The Institute collaborates on a range of projects with other academic programs and practice organizations, nationally and internationally.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.gmu.edu/departments/ICAR/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>756</id>
		<name>International Security Studies at Yale University</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.yale.edu/iss/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>757</id>
		<name>Institute for Latin American and Iberian Studies at Columbia University</name>
		<blurb>For more than 35 years the Institute of Latin American and Iberian Studies (ILAIS) has supported scholarship and professional achievement in the field of Latin American studies. When it was founded in 1962 as one of several regionally-focused centers at Columbia, it was responding to a need to provide the nation with scholars and professionals knowledgeable in what were to most Americans relatively unknown areas of the world. In recent years, as the field as expanded, ILAIS has become a center where students and faculty, often with extensive exposure to the region, come together to exchange ideas and information with a wide range of scholars, businesspeople, government officials, and artists from Latin America and Iberia.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.columbia.edu/cu/ilas/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>758</id>
		<name>Social Science Research Council</name>
		<blurb>Founded in 1923, the Social Science Research Council (SSRC) is an independent, nongovernmental, not-for-profit, international association devoted to the advancement of interdisciplinary research in the social sciences. It does this through a wide variety of interdisciplinary workshops and conferences, fellowships and grants, summer training institutes, scholarly exchanges, and publications. Throughout its program, the SSRC mobilizes eminent social scientists from the United States and abroad to identify and explore new intellectual paths and to test their knowledge, theories, and methods against the challenges of contemporary and historical problems. A central emphasis of the Council is to expand the empirical, theoretical, and methodological bases upon which social science research rests. Fellowship andgrant programs recruit promising pre- and postdoctoral scholars, and provide support for training and development. Other programs seek to improve the resources available to senior researchers and provide opportunities for advanced training.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ssrc.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>759</id>
		<name>Institute for the Study of Diplomacy, Edmund A. Walsh School of Foreign Service, Georgetown University</name>
		<blurb>The Institute for the Study of Diplomacy is part of the Edmund A. Walsh School of Foreign Service at Georgetown University. The Institute focuses on the implementation of foreign policy, seeking to discover how announced policy objectives can best be pursued, by drawing on the concrete experiences of practitioners and the conceptual, comparative, and historical work of academics. Founded in 1978 as part of the Walsh School of Foreign Service, the Institute for the Study of Diplomacy (ISD) has sponsored discussions, research, and publications focused on the implementation of foreign policy. ISD&#039;s larger constituency is the broader academic and policy community. The Institute reaches this group through publications, conferences, working groups, and research activities, which include participation by men and women who make and influence foreign policy.</blurb>
		<url>http://isd.georgetown.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>760</id>
		<name>Institute of International Relations Prague</name>
		<blurb>The Institute of International Relations (IIR) is an independent research organization. It conducts scholarly research, as well as analytical activities concerning international relations and Czech foreign and security policy. It organizes conferences, seminars, and round-table discussions of experts, academics, and political professionals on international relations, security, and development issues.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.iir.cz/?lng=uk</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>764</id>
		<name>The New School Graduate Program in International Affairs</name>
		<blurb>The Graduate Program in International Affairs (GPIA) embodies the distinctive tradition of critical and engaged social thought of the New School. Faculty members combine practical experience in development work, the third sector, or in public advocacy with academic research that engages core problems of globalization and international affairs today. The student body is a diverse, vibrant combination of recent college graduates and professionals who are changing careers or adding to their qualifications.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.gpia.info/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>767</id>
		<name>International Institute at University of Wisconsin, Madison</name>
		<blurb>The International Institute at the University of Wisconsin-Madison is a federation of campus area and international programs; it brings together thirteen programs including six Title VI National Resource Centers as well as other programs and topical programs focusing on global studies, comparative cultures and international relations. The Institute is a strategic partnership between the College of Letters and Science and the Office of International Studies and Programs. Its mission is to (1) support the constituent programs, (2) encourage innovation in research, teaching and outreach, (3) inspire activities that cross regional and disciplinary lines, (4) expand contracts with academic centers in the US and abroad, and (5) develop new alliances with campus interdisciplinary programs, the state and alumni.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.intl-institute.wisc.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>768</id>
		<name>International Peace Institute</name>
		<blurb>The International Peace Institute (IPI) formerly International Peace Academy is an independent, international institution dedicated to promoting the prevention and settlement of armed conflict between and within states through policy research and development.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ipacademy.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>771</id>
		<name>International Studies Association</name>
		<blurb>Columbia International Affairs Online has made available for the first time online papers from the 2000 International Studies Association Annual Meeting. Participation in this experimental project is voluntary. We will continue to post ISA papers as we receive them.</blurb>
		<url>https://www.ciaonet.org/isa/aap01/index.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>772</id>
		<name>Jerusalem Center for Public Affairs</name>
		<blurb>JCPA is an independent, non-profit institute for policy research and education serving Israel and the Jewish people since 1976. The Center is headed by Israel&#039;s former UN Ambassador Dr. Dore Gold. Some 300 researchers have participated in JCPA studies, including 70 Center Fellows and Associates, resulting in over 700 publications in English and Hebrew.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.jcpa.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>774</id>
		<name>Project on Defense Alternatives</name>
		<blurb>Since its inception in 1991, the Project on Defense Alternatives has sought to adapt security policy to the challenges and opportunities of the post-Cold War era. Toward this end it promotes consideration of the broadest range of defense options. Central to its mission is the development of &quot;transitional security policy,&quot; which would serve to create conditions favorable to the advent of regional and global cooperative security regimes. In the Project&#039;s perspective a transitional security policy would: Guarantee reliable, cost-effective defense against aggression; Rely on military structures that do not contribute to interstate tensions, crisis instability, or arms racing; Allow significant reductions in the level of armed forces and military spending; Foster progress in arms control and in the gradual demilitarization of international relations; and, Facilitate an increasing reliance on collective and global peacekeeping agencies and nonmilitary means of conflict prevention, containment, and resolution. In its approach to security issues the Project seeks to uniquely combine pragmatism and vision. Although proceeding from a common security perspective, PDA pays careful attention to concerns about current military threats and requirements. The Project is premised on the belief that policy innovation can overcome the practical obstacles to progress toward more cooperative security postures - however, it sees the prerequisite of innovation to be a close and critical engagement in the mainstream security policy debate. Although PDA emphasizes the reformulation of US defense policy, it has contributed since its inception to the development of defense alternatives for NATO and has pioneered proposals for the &quot;defensive restructuring&quot; of armed forces in Eastern Europe, Russia, and the developing world. As part of this latter effort, the Project has designed arms control measures that would reduce the offensive character of existing conventional armed forces and reorient military assistance programs along defensive lines.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.comw.org/pda/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>775</id>
		<name>International Council on Korean Studies</name>
		<blurb>The International Council on Korean Studies (ICKS or Gukje Hanguk Hakhoi) was found in March 1996 as a non profit and non partisan organization dedicated to the advancement of Korean studies and related academic and professional research in the field of Korean affairs in the United States as well as abroad through international conferences, seminars, publications, and other relevant activities. The Council aims to promote the significance of Korean studies and explore issues of the Korean Reunification among the professionals and the new generation of Koreans and Korean Americans.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.icks.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>776</id>
		<name>The Joan B. Kroc Institute for International Peace Studies, University of Notre Dame</name>
		<blurb>Founded in 1986, The Joan B. Kroc Institute for International Peace Studies at the University of Notre Dame is committed to the principle that peace is inseparable from the resolution of violent conflicts, promotion of human rights, equitable development, and social justice. The Institute conducts research and public outreach on empowering international institutions and enforcing peace, conflicts and conflict theory, globalization, human rights, and religious and ethical views of peace and development. The Institute offers a unique graduate program leading to an M.A. in peace studies, which brings together students from areas of conflict throughout the world.</blurb>
		<url>http://kroc.nd.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>777</id>
		<name>Human Rights First</name>
		<blurb>Human Rights First was founded in 1978 as the Lawyers Committee for International Human Rights to promote laws and policies that advance universal rights and freedoms. We exist to protect and defend the dignity of each individual through respect for human rights and the rule of law.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.humanrightsfirst.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>779</id>
		<name>Liechtenstein Institute on Self Determination, Princeton University</name>
		<blurb>The Liechtenstein Institute on Self-Determination (LISD) supports research, publication, and teaching on self-determination, state sovereignty, boundaries, and autonomy; related sociocultural, ethnic, and religious issues; aspects of international law and international politics; strategic, political, economic, and economic-industrial matters; and the role and character of international organizations such as the UN, the OSCE, and other regional organizations and NGOs in search of greater autonomy or independence. The program is funded through the generosity of H.S.H. Prince Hans Adam II of Liechtenstein, and is directed by program founder Wolfgang Danspeckgruber, lecturer in public and international affairs at the Woodrow Wilson School.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.princeton.edu/~lisd/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>780</id>
		<name>The London School of Economics and Political Science</name>
		<blurb>The London School of Economics and Political Science (LSE) is the leading centre in the UK for teaching and research in the social sciences. The School\&#039;s academic profile spans a wide range of disciplines, from economics, international relations, government and law, to sociology, information systems, and accounting and finance. Teaching and research are conducted through 18 departments and 25 Research Centers and Institutes. The School is renowned for its atmosphere of intellectual argument and debate. No set view prevails; rather, LSE is a laboratory where ideas from all perspectives are developed, tested, criticized and disseminated to the wider world.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.lse.ac.uk/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>781</id>
		<name>Stockholm International Peace Research Institute</name>
		<blurb>In 1964, Prime Minister Tage Erlander of Sweden put forward the idea of establishing a peace research institute to commemorate Sweden&#039;s 150 years of unbroken peace. A Swedish Royal Commission chaired by Ambassador Alva Myrdal proposed in its 1966 report to establish this institute, later named the Stockholm International Peace Research Institute, SIPRI. The Institute&#039;s research should seek to contribute to &quot;the understanding of the preconditions for a stable peace and for peaceful solutions of international conflicts&quot; and the Commission recommended that research be concentrated on armaments, their limitation and reduction, and arms control. The Commission also recommended that SIPRI work be of &quot;an applied research character directed toward practical-political questions [which] should be carried on in a constant interchange with research of a more theoretical kind.&quot;</blurb>
		<url>http://www.sipri.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>783</id>
		<name>Media Tenor International</name>
		<blurb>The Media Tenor Institute is an independent and non partisan organization, founded 10 years ago and based in Bonn, Germany, with offices in Pretoria, South Africa, Ostrava, Czech Republic, London, U.K. and New York, U.S. More than 180 media analysts track and code approximately 250 media from different countries every day. Based on the data, Media Tenor&#039;s research offers an objective understanding of the influence of media on politics, the economy and society. Media Tenor has developed a unique and extremely detailed methodology based on communication science, which can measure media trends without interference from subjective bias and opinion. Recent studies have focused on the presidential elections 2004 in U.S., the coverage of AIDS/HIV, the portrayal of ethnic and racial minorities, country images, anti Americanism in foreign media and more.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.mediatenor.com/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>784</id>
		<name>MIT Center for International Studies</name>
		<blurb>The Center for International Studies (CIS) aims to support and promote international research and education at MIT. Whenever possible, we capitalize on MIT&#039;s great strengths in science and engineering, examining the international aspects of these fields as they relate to both policy and practice, and focusing on those issues where science and engineering intersect most closely with foreign affairs.</blurb>
		<url>http://web.mit.edu/cis</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>785</id>
		<name>Middle East Institute, Columbia University</name>
		<blurb>The Middle East Institute, founded in 1954, has helped to set the national pace in developing an interdisciplinary approach to the study of the Middle East from the rise of Islam to the present, with a primary focus on the 19th and 20th centuries and with specialization in the Arab countries, Armenia, Iran, Israel, Turkey, and Central Asia.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.mei.columbia.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>787</id>
		<name>The National Academy of Public Administration</name>
		<blurb>The National Academy of Public Administration is the preeminent organization dedicated to improving the performance of governance systems-the network of public institutions, nonprofit organizations, and private companies that share in the implementation of public policy. As an independent, nonprofit organization chartered by Congress, the Academy responds to specific requests from public agencies and non-government organizations. The Academy also promotes discourse on emerging trends in governance through its Standing Panels and with external funding.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.napawash.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>788</id>
		<name>New York Academy of Sciences</name>
		<blurb>Founded in 1817, the New York Academy of Sciences is the third oldest scientific organization in America and one of New York City&#039;s oldest and most enduring cultural institutions. The Academy is an independent, nonprofit organization with nearly 50,000 members in more than 160 countries united by a commitment to promoting science and technology and their essential roles in fostering social and economic development.
In service to science, the Academy facilitates communication among scientists, physicians, policy makers, government officers, educators, and journalists from around the world through its interdisciplinary conferences and section meetings and diverse publications. In service to society, Academy Programs draw upon the foremost experts and the most current information about advances in science and technology to inform analysis and discussion of public policy issues, to promote precollege education, and to foster the human rights of scientists.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.nyas.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>789</id>
		<name>The North-South Center, University of Miami</name>
		<blurb>The Dante B. Fascell North-South Center at the University of Miami is an independent research and educational institution committed to promoting better relations among the United States, Canada, and the nations of Latin America and the Caribbean by advancing knowledge and understanding of the major political, social, economic, and cultural issues affecting the citizens of the Western Hemisphere. The Center&#039;s research encompasses issues such as democratic governance, trade and economic policy, sustainable development, migration, civil society participation, and inter-American business and labor issues. This wide range of expertise has distinguished the North-South Center as a reliable resource for policymakers, scholars, and business leaders. Public-private partnerships with institutions in the United States, Latin America, the Caribbean, and Canada enhance the Center&#039;s research and outreach projects by communicating its work with a wide audience. The Center&#039;s research has also played a significant role in framing policy dialogue among key decisionmakers and scholars in the Americas. The North-South Center Press publishes books, monographs, and reports that advance policy-relevant knowledge and understanding of the major contemporary economic, social, political, and cultural issues of Western Hemisphere relations. These publications represent an important resource from which policymakers, business practitioners, students, and professors can derive thoughtful insights, strategic assessments, and up-to-date research on vitally important inter-American policy issues.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.miami.edu/chp/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>790</id>
		<name>The Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development</name>
		<blurb>The Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development is a Paris-based intergovernmental organisation whose purpose is to provide its 29 Member countries with a forum in which governments can compare their experiences, discuss the problems they share and seek solutions which can then be applied within their own national contexts. The Organisation is thus entirely at the service of its Member countries. It forms a homogeneous entity in that each Member country is committed to the principles of the market economy and pluralistic democracy. The fundamental task of the OECD is straightforward: namely to enable its members to consult and co-operate with each other in order to achieve the highest sustainable economic growth in their countries and improve the economic and social well-being of their populations. The OECD offers advice and makes recommendations to its members to help them to define their policies. On occasion its also arbitrates negotiations of multilateral agreements and establishes legal codes in certain areas of activity. The Organisation is a forum for objective, skilled and independent dialogue which permits a thorough understanding and true assessment of the problems posed in today&#039;s increasingly complex world. The great comparative advantages of the OECD are its multidisciplinary approach--a capacity to cover all areas of government activity in a consistent way--and its system of consensus building through peer pressure. Within the different committees the peer pressure system encourages countries to be transparent, to provide explanations and justifications, and to be self-critical where necessary, the practice of self-assessment being the most original characteristic of the OECD.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.oecd.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>791</id>
		<name>Overseas Development Council</name>
		<blurb>The Overseas Development Council (ODC) is an independent, international policy research institution based in Washington, DC, that seeks to improve decision making on multilateral cooperation to promote more effective development and the better management of related global problems. Its program focuses on the interrelationship of globalization and development, and improved multilateral responses to these linked challenges. To this end, ODC provides analysis, information, and evaluation of multilateral policies, actions, and institutions; develops innovative ideas and new policy proposals; and creates opportunities for decision makers and other interested parties to participate in discussions of critical global issues and decisions. NOTE: ODC ceased operations on December 31, 2000. CIAO will maintain an archive of the collected ODC papers.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.odc.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>792</id>
		<name>Oxford Analytica</name>
		<blurb>Founded in 1975, Oxford Analytica is an international consulting firm which provides business and political leaders with timely analysis of worldwide political, economic and social developments. Oxford Analytica acts as a bridge between the world of ideas and the world of enterprise. One of its major assets is an extensive international network which draws on the scholarship and expertise of over 1,000 senior members at Oxford and other leading universities around the world, as well as think-tanks and institutes of international standing. Clients of Oxford Analytica are able to integrate the judgements drawn from this unparalleled resource into their own decision-making process. Clients include multinational corporations, major banks, national governments and international institutions in more than 30 countries.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.oxan.com/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>794</id>
		<name>South Eastern Europe Clearinghouse for the Control of Small Arms and Light Weapons</name>
		<blurb>The South Eastern Europe Clearinghouse for the Control of Small Arms and Light Weapons (SEESAC) was launched on 08 May 2002 in Belgrade. SEESAC is a component of the Regional Implementation Plan on Combating the Proliferations of Small Arms and Light Weapons (SALW) formulated and adopted by the Stability Pact in November 2001, with the aims of stopping the flow and availability of SALW in the region, consolidating achievements so far and supporting the socio-economic conditions for peace and development in South East Europe. The uncontrolled proliferation and illicit trafficking of small arms and light weapons (SALW) is a serious problem in South Eastern Europe. SALW proliferation has fuelled crime and insecurity, exacerbating conflict in the region and undermining post conflict peace-building. Problems related to SALW are likely to pose a serious constraint to economic and social development in South Eastern Europe. Established in co-operation with the UNDP and housed in their offices in Belgrade, SEESAC worked to support the Stability Pact Regional Implementation Plan for an initial period of three years; the impact of the project has led to a further two-year extension until December 2006. Political and strategic guidance and indigenous support for SEESAC is provided by a Regional Steering Group (RSG), which is composed of representatives of the governments of the states concerned, the Stability Pact, UNDP and observers from institutions such as the European Union (EU), North Atlantic Treaty Organisation (NATO), Organisation for Security and Co-operation in Europe (OSCE) and civil society. The RSG meets twice yearly and has approved the 2005 SEESAC Strategy. SEESAC operates under the guidance of The Regional Steering Group for Small Arms and Light Weapons and the UN Resident Co-ordinator in Belgrade. SEESAC liaises directly with governments and civil society, providing technical input, information exchange, co-ordination and overview of current and future efforts and fund-raising assistance for specific SALW projects. SEESAC&#039;s small team is in constant communication with all the governments involved and with the relevant international organisations, non-governmental organisations and bi-lateral donors. SEESAC&#039;s regional activities include sensitising governments and civil society on small arms issues, formulating national strategies for SALW control and incorporating small arms issues into UNDP development planning.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.seesac.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>796</id>
		<name>United States Agency for International Development</name>
		<blurb>The United States Agency for International Development (USAID) is the independent government agency that provides economic development and humanitarian assistance to advance U.S. economic and political interests overseas. Established in 1961 by President John F. Kennedy, USAID has achieved a proud record of accomplishment. In these times of tight federal budgets, many Americans have asked, Why foreign aid? The answers are simple: the small portion of the federal budget that assists developing nations is spent directly in the best interests of the United States and has produced a striking record of accomplishment. Public opinion polls on foreign assistance reveal two important trends: (1) most Americans grossly overestimate the size of America\&#039;s foreign assistance program;and (2) a strong majority of Americans believe modest assistance to the less fortunate reflects American values. In short, America is doing well by doing good through USAID\&#039;s participatory development activities. Further, USAID\&#039;s activities lead to direct economic benefits here at home in almost every state in the Union.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.usaid.gov/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>797</id>
		<name>Institute for Social and Economic Research and Policy at Columbia University</name>
		<blurb>The Institute for Social and Economic Research and Policy (ISERP) is the research arm of the social sciences at Columbia University. ISERP&#039;s mission is to catalyze and produce pioneering social science research and to shape public policy by integrating knowledge and methods across the social science disciplines. The Institute supports a collaborative interdisciplinary community through seminars and research centers; a seed grants program and working paper series; technical and statistical assistance for faculty research; support for grant application and administration; and development and management of large-scale collaborative projects. ISERP also offers social science training at the master&#039;s, doctoral, and postdoctoral level. ISERP is the direct descendant of the pathbreaking Bureau for Applied Social Research (BASR), established at Columbia in 1944 by the sociologist Paul F. Lazarsfeld. One of the first social science institutes in the nation, the Bureau made landmark contributions to communications research, public opinion polling, organizational studies, and social science methodology. BASR&#039;s tradition was carried on by the Center for the Social Sciences, established in 1976 after Lazarsfeld&#039;s death and later renamed to honor him. The Lazarsfeld Center for the Social Sciences was one of the centers incorporated into the Institute at its founding in 1998. A name change in 2001 officially launched Columbia&#039;s Institute for Social and Economic Research and Policy.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.iserp.columbia.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>799</id>
		<name>Public International Law  Policy Group</name>
		<blurb>The Public International Law  Policy Group (PILPG) is a 501(c)(3) non-profit organization, operating as a global pro bono law firm providing free legal assistance to developing states and sub-state entities involved in conflicts. To facilitate the utilization of this legal assistance, PILPG also provides policy formulation advice and training on matters related to conflict resolution. To date, PILPG has advised over a dozen countries on the legal aspects of peace negotiations and constitution-drafting, and over fifteen countries in Europe, Asia, and Africa concerning fundamental questions of public international law.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.publicinternationallaw.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>800</id>
		<name>Ralph Bunche Institute for International Studies, City University of New York</name>
		<blurb>The Ralph Bunche Institute for International Studies engages in research, graduate training, and public education about international affairs and contemporary global problem-solving with a focus on multilateralism and international institutions. Founded in 1973 as the Ralph Bunche Institute on the United Nations, it was renamed in 2001 and given a broader interdisciplinary scope with the mandate to support and further strengthen international studies at The Graduate Center. Under the directorship of Thomas G. Weiss, presidential professor of political science, the institute provides a congenial setting for the activities by faculty and visiting scholars with international portfolios and research; and it facilitates the mentoring of graduate students. The institute is governed by a faculty advisory council. An external advisory board is being reconstituted.</blurb>
		<url>http://web.gc.cuny.edu/RalphBuncheInstitute/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>801</id>
		<name>Raoul-Dandurand Chair</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.dandurand.uqam.ca/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>802</id>
		<name>Centre for International Peace and Security Studies</name>
		<blurb>The Centre for International Peace and Security Studies formalizes research cooperation among Montreal&#039;s leading specialists of world politics, with the aim of integrating the activities of a growing number of faculty, students and experts.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cepsi.umontreal.ca/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>804</id>
		<name>Robert Wood Johnson Health  Society Scholars Program</name>
		<blurb>The Robert Wood Johnson Health  Society Scholars Program is designed to build the nation&#039;s capacity for research, leadership and action to address the broad range of factors affecting the health of populations.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.healthandsocietyscholars.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>808</id>
		<name>Weatherhead Center for International Affairs, Harvard University</name>
		<blurb>The Weather head Center for International Affairs is an autonomous component of Harvard University&#039;s Faculty of Arts and Sciences. It is structured to encourage the highest practical level of personal and intellectual interaction among a diverse community of scholars and practitioners. The Center is distinctive in its recognition that knowledge is a product not only of individual academic research but also of vigorous, sustained intellectual dialogue among scholars and nonacademic experts. To stimulate this dialogue, the Center sponsors a wide array of seminars, research programs, workshops, and conferences. The fruits of Center research are made available to the public policy community through books, articles, reports, seminars, and lectures, as well as through the personal participation of Center members in policy planning and decision making in governments and institutions outside the University.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.wcfia.harvard.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>811</id>
		<name>WaterLife Foundation</name>
		<blurb>The WaterLife Foundation is a New York-based charity designed to engage the corporate sector in small-scale/big impact sustainable drinking water partnerships in the developing world. WaterLife will work with local communities to install new wells, repository systems, sanitation systems, and a variety of other solutions, depending on the local need.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.waterlife.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>813</id>
		<name>U.S. Government Statistics, Economic Statistics Briefing Room</name>
		<blurb>The purpose of this service is to provide easy access to current Federal economic indicators. It provides links to information produced by a number of Federal agencies. All of the information included in the Economic Statistics Briefing Room is maintained and updated by the statistical units of those agencies. All the estimates for the indicators presented in the Federal Statistics Briefing Rooms are the most currently available values.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.gpoaccess.gov/indicators/index.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>815</id>
		<name>China Brief, The Jamestown Foundation</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url></url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>817</id>
		<name>The Mershon Center</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://mershoncenter.osu.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>818</id>
		<name>The Africa Law Institute</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.theafricalawinstitute.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>828</id>
		<name>Palgrave Macmillan</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.palgrave-journals.com/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>829</id>
		<name>Japan Association of International Relations</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.soc.nii.ac.jp/jair/index_en.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>831</id>
		<name>School of International and Public Affairs, Columbia University</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://sipa.columbia.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>832</id>
		<name>Central and East European International Studies Association</name>
		<blurb>The Central and East European International Studies Association (CEEISA) was founded in February 1996 by the members of the International Affairs Network and by the Department of International Relations at St. Petersburg State University. The CEEISA has grown into a major regional organisation of scholars and practitioners in international relations.</blurb>
		<url>http://ian.vse.cz/ceeisa/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>833</id>
		<name>Centre for Military and Strategic Studies</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://cmss.ucalgary.ca/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>834</id>
		<name>Centre for Security Sector Management</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.ssronline.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>835</id>
		<name>Global Research in International Affairs Center, Interdisciplinary Center</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>URL: http://meria.idc.ac.il/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>836</id>
		<name>The Nixon Center</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.nixoncenter.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>838</id>
		<name>James Martin Center for Nonproliferation Studies</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://cns.miis.edu/index.htm</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>839</id>
		<name>Security Studies</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url></url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>841</id>
		<name>Whitehead School of Diplomacy and International Relations, Seton Hall University</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://diplomacy.shu.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>842</id>
		<name>The Harriman Institute</name>
		<blurb>Since its founding in 1946, the Harriman Institute, formerly the Russian Institute, has maintained its position as a leading center for the advancement of knowledge in the field of Russian and Eurasian studies through the research conducted by its faculty, students, fellows and visiting scholars and the training of scholars and professionals.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.harrimaninstitute.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>844</id>
		<name>Centre for European Political Sociology</name>
		<blurb>Centred on a political sociology approach open to interdisciplinary perspectives, the GSPE&#039;s research explores the transformations of public action and the Europeanisation of politics. This broad research thematic can be divided into three main research areas: EU Professionals; Public action in Europe; European public spheres.</blurb>
		<url>http://prisme.u-strasbg.fr/workingpapers/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>845</id>
		<name>Liechtenstein Institute on Self-Determination</name>
		<blurb>The Liechtenstein Institute on Self-Determination supports teaching, research, publication and negotiation about issues pertaining to the state, self-determination, self-governance, sovereignty, security, and boundaries with particular consideration of sociocultural, ethnic, and religious issues; and related legal, diplomatic, economic, strategic, and environmental matters involving state as well as non-state actors. The program is funded through the generosity of H.S.H. Prince Hans Adam II of Liechtenstein, and is directed by program founder Wolfgang Danspeckgruber, lecturer in public and international affairs at the Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs at Princeton University.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.princeton.edu/lisd/index.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>846</id>
		<name>Institute of International Education</name>
		<blurb>An independent nonprofit founded in 1919, IIE is among the world&#039;s largest and most experienced international education and training organizations. We are committed to delivering program excellence to a diverse range of participants, sponsors, and donors.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.iie.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>847</id>
		<name>The Caucasian Review of International Affairs</name>
		<blurb>The Caucasian Review of International Affairs (CRIA) is a Germany-registered, quarterly peer-reviewed free, not-for-profit and online academic journal which has been published in English since 2006. With its broad International Advisory Board and Editorial Board representing various academic institutions the Review is committed to promote a better understanding of regional affairs by providing relevant background information and analysis, as far as the Caucasus in general, and the South Caucasus in particular are concerned.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cria-online.org/Home.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>848</id>
		<name>Centre on Human Rights in Conflict</name>
		<blurb>The primary objective of the Centre on Human Rights in Conflict is to develop policy relevant research and activities in three concrete and contested areas of human rights: human rights in armed conflict, Islam and human rights, and human rights and civil liberties in the war on terrorism, to aid scholars and practitioners working in these areas.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.uel.ac.uk/chrc/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>849</id>
		<name>National Endowment for Democracy</name>
		<blurb>The National Endowment for Democracy (NED) is a private, nonprofit organization created in 1983 to strengthen democratic institutions around the world through nongovernmental efforts. The Endowment is governed by an independent, nonpartisan board of directors. With its annual congressional appropriation, it makes hundreds of grants each year to support prodemocracy groups in Africa, Asia, Central and Eastern Europe, Latin America, the Middle East, and the former Soviet Union. The publication listed below are produced by The Center for International Media Assistance (CIMA) http://cima.ned.org/, an initiative of NED which aims to strengthen the support, raise the visibility, and improve the effectiveness of media assistance programs throughout the world. The Center approaches its mission by providing information, building networks, conducting research, and highlighting the indispensable role independent media play in the creation and development of sustainable democracies around the world.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ned.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>850</id>
		<name>Columbia Center on Sustainable Investment</name>
		<blurb>The Columbia Center on Sustainable Investment (CCSI), a joint center of Columbia Law School and the Earth Institute at Columbia University, is a leading applied research center and forum dedicated to the study, practice and discussion of sustainable international investment. Our mission is to develop and disseminate practical approaches and solutions, as well as to analyze topical policy-oriented issues, in order to maximize the impact of international investment for sustainable development. The Center undertakes its mission through interdisciplinary research, advisory projects, multi-stakeholder dialogue, educational programs, and the development of resources and tools.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ccsi.columbia.edu. </url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>851</id>
		<name>The Objective Standard</name>
		<blurb>The Objective Standard is a quarterly journal of culture and politics based on the idea that for every human concern from personal matters to foreign policy, from the sciences to the arts, from education to legislation there are demonstrably objective standards by reference to which we can assess what is true or false, good or bad, right or wrong. The purpose of the journal is to analyze and evaluate ideas, trends, events, and policies accordingly.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.theobjectivestandard.com/index.asp</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>853</id>
		<name>Georgetown University Press</name>
		<blurb>Georgetown University Press supports the academic mission of Georgetown University by publishing scholarly books and journals for a diverse, worldwide readership. These publications, written by an international group of authors representing a broad range of intellectual perspectives, reflect the academic and institutional strengths of the university. We publish peer-reviewed works of academic distinction, with exceptional editorial and production quality, in five subjects: bioethics; international affairs  human rights; languages  linguistics; political science, public policy  public management; and religion  ethics.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.press.georgetown.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>854</id>
		<name>Center for Contemporary Arab Studies</name>
		<blurb>Dean of School of International Affairs at Azerbaijan Diplomatic Academy. The Center for Contemporary Arab Studies (CCAS) is the only academic center in the United States focusing essentially on the Arab world--the region from Morocco to the Gulf. It has been doing so with distinction for over 30 years. The Center&#039;s Washington, DC location provides access to government, the non-governmental policy-studies community, the media, and business as well as academia. Attendance at its public events and applications to its distinguished Masters Degree Program in Arab Studies (MAAS) have more than doubled since 2001.</blurb>
		<url>http://ccas.georgetown.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>855</id>
		<name>Department of Economics and Business, Colorado College</name>
		<blurb>Welcome to the Department of Economics and Business. Our department provides students with rigorous grounding in economic and business concepts. It also provides outstanding preparation for careers in business and public service. In addition, many of the department&#039;s alumni pursue graduate study at the nation&#039;s finest business and law schools, as well as doctoral work in economics at leading research universities.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.coloradocollege.edu/academics/dept/economics/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>856</id>
		<name>Oxford Economics</name>
		<blurb>Economics matters. Combining skilled analysis with detailed information on the global economic environment creates a firm base for your decisions. Oxford Economics was founded in 1981 as a commercial venture with Oxford University&#039;s business college to provide economic advice, forecasts and analytical tools to international institutions, governments and blue-chip companies. Building on these foundations, we are now an independently-owned world-leader in high quality, quantitative analysis and evidence-based business and public policy advice.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.oxfordeconomics.com/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>857</id>
		<name>The Polish Institute of International Affairs</name>
		<blurb>The Polish Institute of International Affairs (PISM) was set up under an act of Parliament dated December 20, 1996. The organisation of the Institute commenced in 1999 and the first employees joined PISM in 2000.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.pism.pl/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>858</id>
		<name>Weatherhead East Asian Institute</name>
		<blurb>Since its establishment in 1949, Columbia University&#039;s East Asian Institute has been a major center for research, teaching, and publishing on modern and contemporary Asia, covering China, Japan, Taiwan, Hong Kong, the Korean peninsula, and the countries of Southeast Asia; in recent years the scope has expanded to include Tibet and Inner Asia. The Institute is affiliated with Columbia&#039;s Schools of Business, Law, International and Public Affairs, and Arts and Sciences, bringing together over 50 full-time faculty, a diverse group of visiting scholars and professionals, and students from the United States and abroad. As of January 2003, the East Asian Institute was renamed the Weather head East Asian Institute to honor the generosity of the Weather head Foundation.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.columbia.edu/cu/weai/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>860</id>
		<name>Centre for European Security Studies</name>
		<blurb>The Centre for European Security Studies is an independent non-governmental organisation based in the north of the Netherlands. From our tiny office in the old university town of Groningen, we run programmes that focus on democracy in the realm of defence and security. Our mission is to promote transparent, accountable and effective government in the security sector. In pursuit of this aim, we conduct research, provide policy advice, hold debates, organise roundtable discussions and offer training courses. We are able to carry out such a wide range of activities thanks to the co-operation of a wide network experts and partners, mostly based in Europe. The results of these collaborative efforts are presented here under the headings publications and events. Our work is also made possible by the support of governmental and independent sponsors.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cess.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>861</id>
		<name>Norwegian Peacebuilding Resource Centre</name>
		<blurb>Noref - Norsk Ressurssenter for Fredsbygging - is a resource centre integrating knowledge and experience to strengthen peacebuilding policy and practice.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.peacebuilding.no/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>862</id>
		<name>Africa Center for Strategic Studies</name>
		<blurb>The Africa Center is the pre-eminent Department of Defense institution for strategic security studies, research, and outreach in Africa. The Africa Center engages African partner states and institutions through rigorous academic and outreach programs that build strategic capacity and foster long-term, collaborative relationships.</blurb>
		<url>http://africacenter.org/home/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>863</id>
		<name>Transparency International</name>
		<blurb>Transparency International, the global civil society organisation leading the fight against corruption, brings people together in a powerful worldwide coalition to end the devastating impact of corruption on men, women and children around the world. TI&#039;s mission is to create change towards a world free of corruption. Transparency International challenges the inevitability of corruption, and offers hope to its victims. Since its founding in 1993, TI has played a lead role in improving the lives of millions around the world by building momentum for the anti-corruption movement. TI raises awareness and diminishes apathy and tolerance of corruption, and devises and implements practical actions to address it.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.transparency.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>864</id>
		<name>Centre for Strategic Research and Analysis</name>
		<blurb>CESRAN is, a non-partisan and non-profit organisation, is founded by Turkish academics but headquartered in the UK to become an international think-tank and forum regardless of any race and religion. The CESRAN webpage at www.cesran.org publishes news articles, commentary, background research and analysis on a broad range of issues, focussing on social, economic, strategic and environmental processes. CESRAN publishes an academic, peer-reviewed Journal (Journal of Global Analysis) and a news-magazine (Political Reflection).</blurb>
		<url>http://cesran.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>865</id>
		<name>Global Political Trends Center</name>
		<blurb>Global Political Trends Center (GPoT) is a nonprofit, nonpartisan research institution established under the auspices of Istanbul Kültür University in 2008. Our mission is to conduct high quality, independent and innovative research and education, acting as a link between policy-making institutions, academia, civil society and the media.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.gpotcenter.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>867</id>
		<name>Maritime Institute of Malaysia</name>
		<blurb>The Maritime Institute of Malaysia (MIMA) is a policy research institute set up by the Malaysian Government to look into matters relating to Malaysia&#039;s interest at sea, and to serve as a national focal point for research in the maritime sector. MIMA was incorporated under the Companies Act 1965, as a company limited by guarantee and not having a share capital, with its own Board of Directors.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.mima.gov.my/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>868</id>
		<name>Columbia University World Leaders Forum</name>
		<blurb>Established in 2003 by Lee C. Bollinger, the World Leaders Forum is a year-round event series aimed to advance lively, uninhibited dialogue on the large economic, political, and social questions of our time.The Forum\&#039;s roster of past participants features many of heads of state, in addition to other global thought leaders from a broad spectrum of fields and all regions of the world. A few of the many remarkable past participants are Presidents Bill Clinton, Nicolas Sarkozy of France, Vladimir Putin of Russia, Michelle Bachelet of Chile, Václav Klaus of the Czech Republic, and the Dalai Lama. World Leaders Forum events have garnered press coverage by news media organizations including the Associated Press, the BBC, and PBS, among others.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.worldleaders.columbia.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>869</id>
		<name>Centre for Non-Traditional Security (NTS) Studies</name>
		<blurb>The mission of the Centre for NTS Studies is to conduct research and produces policy-relevant analyses aimed at furthering awareness and building capacity to address NTS issues and challenges in the Asia-Pacific region and beyond.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.rsis.edu.sg/nts/home.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>870</id>
		<name>Institute of Foreign Policy Studies, University of Calcutta</name>
		<blurb>Researh and training programmes in foreign policy issues with particular focus on the South Asian, East Asian, Southeast Asian and the West Asian regions with special emphasis on the international border zones of India [i.e., North Eastern region, Southern region, etc.]. The programme will consists of policy oriented and region specific research projects along with a general M.Phil. Course and short-term certificate/ diploma course for fresh and mid-career level personnel in the MEA as well as other government services.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.caluniv.ac.in/ifps/index.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>871</id>
		<name>The Goettingen Journal of International Law</name>
		<blurb>The Goettingen Journal of International Law is an initiative with the primary objective of publishing an e-journal of legal scholarship focusing on International Law. Our aim is to publish a journal that fosters debate among scholars of diverse fields in international law, while, at the same time, facilitating contributions to the debate from related disciplines. GoJIL publishes two types of issues. The first type is a semi-annual regular issue. For this we encourage submissions addressing international law in general employing methodologies from neighboring disciplines such as international relations, history, or economics. The journal also welcomes contributions emanating from specialized branches of international law such as international criminal law, international humanitarian law, and international economic law.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.gojil.eu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>872</id>
		<name>Macalester College</name>
		<blurb>Macalester is committed to being a preeminent liberal arts college with an educational program known for its high standards for scholarship and its special emphasis on internationalism, multiculturalism, and service to society.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.macalester.edu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>873</id>
		<name>The Global Centre for the Responsibility to Protect</name>
		<blurb>The Responsibility to Protect - known as R2P - refers to the obligation of states toward their populations and toward all populations at risk of genocide and other large-scale atrocities. This new international norm stipulates that: The primary responsibility to protect populations from mass atrocities lies with the state itself. When a state proves either unable or unwilling to protect peoples, that responsibility shifts to the international community. This obligation must be exercised preventively; states can not delay action until mass crimes have already occurred. The tools of action include diplomatic, legal, and other peaceful measures; coercive measures such as sanctions; and, as a last resort, military force. These principles originated in a 2001 report of the International Commission on Intervention and State Sovereignty and were endorsed by the United Nations General Assembly in the 2005 World Summit Outcome Document paragraphs 138 and 139. The UN Secretary General released a report in January 2009 Implementing the Responsibility to Protect. In a July 2009 General Assembly Debate, UN Member States overwhelmingly reaffirmed the 2005 Commitment and passed a consensus resolution taking note of the Secretary-General&#039;s report. Read more about the historic debate here.</blurb>
		<url>http://globalr2p.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>874</id>
		<name>Center for World-Class Universities</name>
		<blurb>The history of the study of world-class universities at Shanghai Jiao Tong University began with the founding of Institute of Higher Education in 1985. The first book (in Chinese) on world-class universities, Research on World-Class Universities edited by then director, Professor Ai Zhu Tao, was published in 1993. In 2007, the first text in English, titled World-Class University and Ranking: Aiming Beyond Status, was published. It was edited by Professor Nian Cai Liu, the director of IHE and by Dr. Jan Sadlak, the director of UNESCO - European Centre for Higher Education.In 2005, the Center for World-Class Universities (CWCU) was named as a strategic research unit by the Chinese Ministry of Education. This acknowledgment was made in recognition of its long tradition of providing high-quality consultation reports to the Chinese government on strategies for building world-class universities and other S policies. Many of these reports have attracted the attention of national leadership, government officials, university leaders and the general public.</blurb>
		<url>http://gse.sjtu.edu.cn/EN/centers.htm</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>875</id>
		<name>Kolleg-Forschergruppe &quot;The Transformative Power of Europe&quot;</name>
		<blurb>The Kolleg-Forschergruppe (KFG) is a new funding programme launched by the German Research Foundation in 2008. As a research college, it is intended to provide a scientifically stimulating environment in which innovative research topics can be dealt with by discourse and debate within a small group of senior and junior researchers. Key characteristics are a comprehensive Fellow Programme for guest scholars from elsewhere in Germany and from abroad, the promotion of young researchers and the opportunity to be released from teaching duties for a set period of time. The KFG &quot;The Transformative Power of Europe&quot; is one of three research colleges, which the DFG approved in the first funding period.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.polsoz.fu-berlin.de/en/v/transformeurope/index.html</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>876</id>
		<name>Central European University</name>
		<blurb>Central European University is a graduate institution in the social sciences, the humanities, law and management. It is accredited in both the United States and Hungary, and offers English-language Master&#039;s and doctoral programs. Located in the heart of Central Europe -- Budapest, Hungary -- CEU has developed a distinct academic and intellectual focus, combining the comparative study of the region&#039;s historical, cultural, and social diversity with a global perspective on good governance, sustainable development and social transformation. As part of its educational, research, and civic engagement activities, CEU attaches particular importance to scholarship relevant to public policy.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.ceu.hu/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>877</id>
		<name>Council of the Americas</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.americasquarterly.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>878</id>
		<name>Center for Strategic Research</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>www.csr.ir/center.aspx?lng=en</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>879</id>
		<name>Değişim Yayınları</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.degisimkitap.com/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>880</id>
		<name>University of Defence</name>
		<blurb>In accordance with the University Act the University of Defence is a university-type school. It was built as of 1 September 2004 to continue utilising the pedagogical and physical potential of the three former military colleges-Brno Military Academy, Military University of the Ground Forces (Vyskov) and Purkyne Military Academy (Hradec Kralove). University of Defence (UoD) primary mission is propagation of literacy, development of thinking and independent scientific research in the issues vital for Czech Republic security or accomplishment of its Alliance obligations. UoD scope of work is defined with focuses of education, formation and training of military professionals as required by the Army of the Czech Republic (ACR) and research projects in favour of the Ministry of Defence (MoD) department.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.unob.cz/en/Default.aspx</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>881</id>
		<name>The Sexual Violence Research Initiative</name>
		<blurb>Sexual violence is a violation of human rights and a serious public health problem. It has a profound impact on physical and mental health, both immediately and many years after the assault. To date, sexual violence has received insufficient attention from researchers, policy-makers and programme designers and it has been a long struggle to have it recognised as a legitimate public health issue. The SVRI is an important contribution to eliminating sexual violence by simultaneously addressing the lack of research on the different aspects of sexual violence as well as drawing attention of a wide range of people including policy makers and the media, to this important public health issue.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.svri.org/index.htm</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>882</id>
		<name>National Defense University Press</name>
		<blurb>The vision of NDU Press is to lead the National Defense University Enterprise in publishing and disseminating vital and complex defense and national security scholarship in a variety of media to inform and influence defense and policy decision makers, as well as the joint professional military education community and interested public.</blurb>
		<url>http://cco.dodlive.mil/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>883</id>
		<name>The Joan B. Kroc Institute for Peace  Justice, University of San Diego</name>
		<blurb>Since 2000, the Joan B. Kroc Institute for Peace  Justice (IPJ) has been in the field working with local partners in conflict-affected countries to bring together governments, the military, human rights advocates, and civil society, particularly marginalized groups, to address the inequalities that fuel conflict and find paths to sustainable peace. Through dialogue, training, negotiations and advocacy, the Institute includes social justice in peace processes in order to prevent a cycle of violence. As part of the University of San Diego&#039;s Joan B. Kroc School of Peace Studies, the Institute employs best practices in peacebuilding and uses its experience on the ground to inform academics and practitioners on effective peacebuilding strategies and techniques.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.sandiego.edu/peacestudies/ipj/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>884</id>
		<name>The Diplomatic Courier</name>
		<blurb>The Diplomatic Courier is an independent publication both in its voice and its organization. Publishing opinions from all political spectrums, the Courier adheres to the ideals of freedom of expression, individualism, and fair and balanced journalism.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.diplomaticourier.com/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>885</id>
		<name>Sakarya University, Institute of Social Sciences</name>
		<blurb>The mission of the University is to contribute in the making of individuals who are keen on producing technology, willing to share and equipped with aesthetic values. The University also aims at providing a contemporary learning/teaching environment in which individuals are given enough opportunities to be competent professionals who respect social values.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.sakarya.edu.tr/en/?pid=iletisim=kampus</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>886</id>
		<name>The Center for Foreign Policy and Peace Research</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.foreignpolicyandpeace.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>887</id>
		<name>Munk School of Global Affairs at the University of Toronto</name>
		<blurb>The Munk School for Global Affairs at the University of Toronto is an interdisciplinary academic centre on global issues that integrates research with teaching and public education. It is home to the Asian Institute, the Centre for European, Russian, and Eurasian Studies, the Canada Centre for Global Security Studies and 30 other centres, institutes, and programs.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.jilir.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>892</id>
		<name>Sakarya University</name>
		<blurb>Our Mission is to discipline individuals avid for discoveries in knowledge and technology to create a contemporary educational culture participatory, sharing, novel and equipped with aesthetic values to educate individuals possessing occupational adequacy and respect for social values.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.sakarya.edu.tr/en/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>893</id>
		<name>EGMONT - The Royal Institute for International Relations</name>
		<blurb>EGMONT-The Royal Institute for International Relations is an independent think-tank based in Brussels. Its interdisciplinary research is conducted in a spirit of total academic freedom. Drawing on the expertise of its own research fellows, as well as that of external specialists, both Belgian and foreign, it provides analysis and suggests international policy options that are meant to be as operational as possible. Benefiting from the role acquired by Brussels in the global arena and from the prestigious setting of the Egmont Palace, the Institute offers an ideal forum to visiting Heads of State, Heads of government, representatives of international organisations, foreign ministers and other political figures. Conferences, colloquia and seminars nurture the work of the research fellows. They also give participants the opportunity to exchange views with other specialists and with a well-informed public made up of representatives of the political, economic and academic spheres, the media and civil society. Along with research and meetings, the Institute has also developed specialised training activities, both in Brussels and abroad. It can, on request, offer specific programmes for visiting and resident diplomats and foreign professionals. Closer collaboration with other research centres, both in Belgium and in the rest of Europe and beyond, has resulted in a growing number of joint conferences and in more structured cooperation on research and publications. It has proved to be mutually beneficial and enriching.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.egmontinstitute.be/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>895</id>
		<name>Harvard Kennedy School</name>
		<blurb>The Kennedy School is committed to both thought and action. Our renowned  faculty and pioneering research centers deliver bold new ideas. Our  students are prepared and trained to lead, no matter whether in the  private, public or non-profit sector. We not only convene the best and  brightest international leaders in engaging today&#039;s top issues, we are  international ourselves. Learn more about us.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.hks.harvard.edu/about</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>897</id>
		<name>International Strategic Studies Doctoral Program</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.ufrgs.br/ppgeei/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>898</id>
		<name>International Strategic Research Organization (USAK)</name>
		<blurb>Established in 2004, the International Strategic Research Organisation (USAK) has gained wide recognition as Turkey&#039;s foremost source of independent and balanced information and research on a broad range of issues affecting Turkey and its region. Focusing particularly on issues of security and cooperation, USAK is one of Turkey and the world&#039;s leading organisations for the analysis of global issues, satisfying a need in Turkey, its region and the world for a body of informed opinion on these issues.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.usak.org.tr/index.php?dil=ing</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>899</id>
		<name>Institute for the Study of War</name>
		<blurb>The Institute for the Study of War advances an informed understanding of military affairs through reliable research, trusted analysis, and innovative education. We are committed to improving the nation&#039;s ability to execute military operations and respond to emerging threats in order to achieve U.S. strategic objectives. ISW is a non-partisan, non-profit, public policy research organization.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.understandingwar.org</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>900</id>
		<name>Third Way</name>
		<blurb>Third Way represents Americans in the &quot;vital center&quot; - those who believe in pragmatic solutions and principled compromise, but who too often are ignored in Washington. Our mission is to advance moderate policy and political ideas. Our agenda includes: a series of grand economic bargains, a new approach to the climate crisis, progress on social issues like immigration reform, marriage for gay couples, tighter gun safety laws, and a credible alternative to neoconservative security policy. Unlike traditional think tanks, we do not house scholars who work in silos on academic research. Instead, we are built around policy teams that create high-impact written products and innovative trainings to influence today&#039;s debates.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.thirdway.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>901</id>
		<name>Hudson Institute</name>
		<blurb>Founded in 1961 by strategist Herman Kahn, Hudson Institute challenges conventional thinking and helps manage strategic transitions to the future through interdisciplinary studies in defense, international relations, economics, health care, technology, culture, and law.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.hudson.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>902</id>
		<name>International Foundation for Electoral Systems</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://www.ifes.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>903</id>
		<name>Atlantic Council</name>
		<blurb>The Atlantic Council promotes constructive leadership and engagement in international affairs based on the Atlantic Community&#039;s central role in meeting global challenges. The Council provides an essential forum for navigating the dramatic economic and political changes defining the twenty-first century by informing and galvanizing its uniquely influential network of global leaders. Through the papers we write, the ideas we generate, and the communities we build, the Council shapes policy choices and strategies to create a more secure and prosperous world. Founded in 1961, the Council provides an essential forum for navigating the dramatic shifts in economic and political influence that are shaping the twenty-first century by educating and galvanizing its uniquely influential, nonpartisan network of international political, business, and intellectual leaders.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.atlanticcouncil.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>905</id>
		<name>The Soufan Group</name>
		<blurb>The Soufan Group provides strategic security intelligence services to governments and multinational organizations. Our training programs, security services, and research insights arm our clients with the essential knowledge and skills to prepare for, manage and respond to constantly evolving security needs.</blurb>
		<url>http://soufangroup.com/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>906</id>
		<name>Foreign Policy Research Institute</name>
		<blurb>The Foreign Policy Research Institute was founded in 1955 by Robert Strausz-Hupe on the premise that, as he put it, &quot;a nation should think before it acts.&quot; Strausz-Hupe is said to have introduced geopolitics into the American vocabulary, which is simply the use of history, geography, and culture to illuminate contemporary international affairs and undergird recommendations for policies that advance the national interest -- a tradition that FPRI maintains to this day. Unique among the think tanks but derivative from its orientation toward history, it sponsors the Butcher History Institute, a nationally recognized professional development program for high school teachers that enjoys participation by faculty from over 700 schools in 46 states. FPRI publishes Orbis, a quarterly journal of world affairs, and E-Notes, circulated weekly by email to readers in over 85 countries. It&#039;s Marvin Wachman Center for Civic and International Literacy offers programming in Philadelphia, Princeton, New York City, and Washington DC.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.fpri.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>907</id>
		<name>Turkish Review</name>
		<blurb>Turkish Review is an English-language magazine published six times a year. We aim to act as a forum for both peer-reviewed academic articles and journalistic pieces on Turkey&#039;s politics, society, economy, culture and history, explored within domestic and international contexts. That is, we are a review of three things: events within Turkey; developments outside of but relevant to Turkey; and global affairs from a Turkish perspective. By &quot;Turkish perspective&quot; we mean adopting a constructive approach, with an inter-disciplinary, inclusive, in-depth and insightful attitude, while maintaining accessibility, originality and objectivity; above all making use of constructive, non-Orientalist, de-colonialist and dialogic language. Turkey lies at the center of (and is itself) a diverse geography, and the wide-ranging texts and backgrounds of our contributors reflect this. The opinions represented and conclusions drawn are those of the authors alone, and do not in any way construe endorsement by Turkish Review, its parent company, or affiliate organizations.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.turkishreview.org/mainAction.action</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>908</id>
		<name>Center for Migration Studies of New York</name>
		<blurb>The Center for Migration Studies of New York (CMS) is an educational institute/think tank devoted to the study of international migration, to the promotion of understanding between immigrants and receiving communities, and to public policies that safeguard the dignity and rights of migrants, refugees and newcomers (www.cmsny.org). CMS was established in 1964 and formally incorporated in 1969 by the Congregation of the Missionaries of St. Charles, Scalabrinians, an international community of Catholic priests, nuns and lay people dedicated to serving migrants and refugees. CMS is a member of the Scalabrini International Migration Network (SIMN), a global network of more than 270 entities that provide services to migrants, including shelters along migrant corridors and welcoming (integration) centers in receiving communities.</blurb>
		<url>http://cmsny.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>909</id>
		<name>Natural Resource Governance Institute </name>
		<blurb>The Natural Resource Governance Institute (NRGI) helps people to realize the benefits of their countries’ endowments of oil, gas and minerals. We do this through technical advice, advocacy, applied research, policy analysis, and capacity development. We work with innovative agents of change within government ministries, civil society, the media, legislatures, the private sector, and international institutions to promote accountable and effective governance in the extractive industries.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.resourcegovernance.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>910</id>
		<name>EuroMeSCo</name>
		<blurb>EuroMeSCo (the Euro-Mediterranean Study Commission) is the main network of research centres on politics and security in the Mediterranean. EuroMeSCo was set up in 1996 with the goal of fostering research, information and social relations among its members as well as acting as a confidence-building measure in the framework of the Barcelona process. EuroMeSCo comprises 102 institutes coming from 32 countries out of the 43 members of the Union for the Mediterranean.

</blurb>
		<url>http://www.euromesco.net/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>911</id>
		<name>Center for a New American Security </name>
		<blurb>The mission of the Center for a New American Security (CNAS) is to develop strong, pragmatic and principled national security and defense policies. Building on the expertise and experience of its staff and advisors, CNAS engages policymakers, experts and the public with innovative, fact-based research, ideas and analysis to shape and elevate the national security debate. A key part of our mission is to inform and prepare the national security leaders of today and tomorrow.</blurb>
		<url>http://www.cnas.org/ </url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>912</id>
		<name>BILGESAM (Wise Men Center for Strategic Studies) </name>
		<blurb>BILGESAM conducts scientific research on bilateral and multilateral issues, on Turkey&#039;s security strategies, and on domestic political, economic, technological, environmental, and socio-cultural problems.  </blurb>
		<url>www.bilgesam.org/en </url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>913</id>
		<name>IEMed European Institute of the Mediterranian </name>
		<blurb>IEMed’s actions are focused on five core themes that make up the Institute’s different working areas: Euro-Mediterranean policies and Euromed regional programmes, socio-economic development, the Arab and Mediterranean world, Mediterranean cultures and cultural action. The different work areas are in line with the Euro-Mediterranean agenda and its strategic objectives. Projects in these areas are programmed in various formats: international symposia, seminars, workshops, debates, talks, research projects, exhibitions, cultural projects, as well as an extensive range of publications and specific studies.

</blurb>
		<url>http://www.iemed.org/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>914</id>
		<name>The Finnish Institute for International Affairs</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url></url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>915</id>
		<name>Turkish Journal for Middle Eastern Studies</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url>http://dergipark.ulakbim.gov.tr/tocd/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>916</id>
		<name>The Ambassadors Review</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url></url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>917</id>
		<name>Center for International Cooperation</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url></url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>918</id>
		<name>Global Peace Operations</name>
		<blurb></blurb>
		<url></url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>919</id>
		<name>The Quality of Government Institute. University of Gothenburg. </name>
		<blurb>The QoG Institute was founded in 2004 by Professor Bo Rothstein and Professor Sören Holmberg. It is an independent research institute within the Department of Political Science at the University of Gothenburg. We are 30 researchers who conduct and promote research on the causes, consequences and nature of Good Governance and the Quality of Government (QoG) - that is, trustworthy, reliable, impartial, uncorrupted and competent government institutions.

While Quality of Government is our common intellectual focal point, we apply a variety of theoretical and methodological perspectives.

The main objective of our research is to address the theoretical and empirical problem of how political institutions of high quality can be created and maintained. A second objective is to study the effects of Quality of Government on a number of policy areas, such as health, the environment, social policy, and poverty. We approach these problems from a variety of different theoretical and methodological angles.
</blurb>
		<url>http://qog.pol.gu.se</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>920</id>
		<name>Varieties of Democracy Institute (V-Dem)</name>
		<blurb>The V-Dem Institute is an independent research institute based at the Department of Political Science, University of Gothenburg, Sweden. The Institute was founded by Professor Staffan I. Lindberg in 2014. The Institute is based at one of the two institutional homes of the V-Dem Project, Kellogg Institute at the University of Notre Dame being the other one. On a regular basis V-Dem is producing a number of different publications such as Working Papers, Country Reports and Briefs, Policy Reports and Briefs, and Thematic Reports. The V-Dem Institute is in charge of most operations relating to data collection at V-Dem Project.

V-Dem Project is a new approach to conceptualization and measurement of democracy. V-Dem has released its complete dataset as global public good, covering some 15 million data points across 173 countries. It includes about 350 unique and disaggregated democracy indicators, 34 mid-level indices, and 5 high-level indices from 1900 until today. Unlike any extant data set, V-Dem has worked with over 2,500 local and cross-national experts to provide evaluations on the many indicators on democracy. 

The dataset is the largest of its kind, enabling a vast research agenda and nuanced descriptive analyses that are comparable across time and space. In September 2016, V-Dem became the recipient of the Lijphart/Przeworski/Verba Dataset Award 2016.

</blurb>
		<url>https://www.v-dem.net/en/</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>921</id>
		<name>Mitvim: The Israeli Institute for Regional Foreign Policies </name>
		<blurb>Mitvim - The Israeli Institute for Regional Foreign Policies is an independent think tank that envisions a fresh start for Israel among the nations. It aims to reshape Israel&#039;s relations in the Middle East, Europe and the Mediterranean, by promoting new paradigms for Israel&#039;s foreign policies, enhancing Israel&#039;s regional belonging, and advancing Israeli-Arab peace. Mitvim works at the political, diplomatic and public levels. It is comprised of Israeli experts, strategists, scholars, and journalists. Mitvim engages in the various phases of the policymaking-cycle and promotes the actual crafting of the regional realities it aspires for. Mitvim generates knowledge, articulates ideas, plans policies, promotes recommendations, and facilitates implementation. It was established in May 2011, and is ranked among the top think tanks in the Middle East and North Africa, according to the University of Pennsylvania&#039;s rankings. </blurb>
		<url>http://www.mitvim.org.il</url>
	</institution>
	<institution>
		<id>922</id>
		<name>Center for International and Regional Studies: CIRS</name>
		<blurb>Established in 2005, the Center for International and Regional Studies (CIRS) at Georgetown University in Qatar is a premier research institute devoted to the academic study of regional and international issues through dialogue and exchange of ideas, research and scholarship, and engagement with national and international scholars, opinion-makers, practitioners, and activists.

Guided by the principles of academic excellence, forward vision, and community engagement, the Center for International and Regional Studies (CIRS) mission revolves around five principal goals:
•	To provide a forum for scholarship and research on international and regional affairs
•	To encourage in-depth examination and exchange of ideas
•	To foster thoughtful dialogue among students, scholars and practitioners of international affairs
•	To facilitate the free flow of ideas and knowledge through publishing the products of its research, sponsoring conferences and seminars, and holding workshops designed to explore the complexities of the twenty-first century
•	To engage in outreach activities with a wide range of local, regional and international partners.
</blurb>
		<url>https://cirs.georgetown.edu</url>
	</institution>
</institutions>
